[{"value": {"id": 1746147, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17262", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of Parole Board recommendations on moving (a) prisoners serving an Imprisonment for Public Protection sentence and (b) other prisoners to open conditions were rejected by the Governme", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17260", "17261"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4056, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "In the response to PQ 15952, it was explained that the transfer of an indeterminate sentence prisoner to open conditions is a decision for the Secretary of State. It was also explained that there is no current power for the Government to overrule a Parole...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Open Prisons", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17260", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17261", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746146, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17261", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2024 to Question 15952, on Prisoners, how many and what proportion of Parole Board recommendations on releasing (a) prisoners serving an Imprisonment for Public Protection se", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17260", "17262"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4056, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "In the response to PQ 15952, it was explained that the transfer of an indeterminate sentence prisoner to open conditions is a decision for the Secretary of State. It was also explained that there is no current power for the Government to overrule a Parole...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parole", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17260", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17262", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746145, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17260", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2024 to Question 15952 on Prisoners, how many and what proportion of Parole Board recommendations were rejected by the Government in each of the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17261", "17262"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4056, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "In the response to PQ 15952, it was explained that the transfer of an indeterminate sentence prisoner to open conditions is a decision for the Secretary of State. It was also explained that there is no current power for the Government to overrule a Parole...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parole", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17261", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17262", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746264, "askingMemberId": 5223, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17399", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to ensure adequate levels of funding for healthcare in Dartford.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Dartford", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746046, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17065", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his policy is on (a) doctors and (b) other qualified medical personnel administering pain-relieving drugs which may shorten lives; and whether regulations on that issue changed after the convi", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Analgesics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746046", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746166, "askingMemberId": 4918, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17277", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding the Government provides for research into a cure for Parkinson's disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parkinson's Disease: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746154, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17186", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish his Department\u2019s pathway for reaching 2.5% of GDP being spent on Defence; and whether he has made any changes to that timetable since 1 November.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 483, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "As the Prime Minister has confirmed the path to spending 2.5% of GDP on Defence will be set out in spring 2025. ", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746376, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17481", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the timeline for the introduction of the Multi-Role Support Ships remains on track to meet operational requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 483, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Multi-Role Strike Ship (MRSS) programme will recapitalise the Royal Navy (RN)\u2019s amphibious fleet, which consists of the three Bay class landing ships (RFA Lyme Bay, Mounts Bay and Cardigan Bay) and RFA Argus, which provides medical and aviation suppor...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Multi-role Ocean Surveillance Ships", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746376", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746353, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17272", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Autumn Budget 2024 on the defence sector.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 483, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Budget increased defence spending in real terms by \u00a32.9 billion for next year and we are committed to setting a path to 2.5% of GDP on defence. The Department's Statement of Intent regarding the Defence Industrial Strategy was published on 2 December....", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Industry", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746353", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746373, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17478", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of retiring HMS Albion and HMS Bulwark on the ability of the Armed Forces to conduct amphibious operations; and how amphibious troops will undertake", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17148", "17149", "17476", "17477"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The retirement of HMS Albion and Bulwark will not impact the operational programme of the Royal Marines, who continue to deploy globally. Both are currently held at lower readiness having not been to sea since 2023 and 2017 respectively. This Government i...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Albion and HMS Bulwark", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17148", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17149", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17476", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17477", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746373", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746372, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17477", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the capability of RFA Argus to fulfil the UK's amphibious operational requirements in the absence of HMS Albion and HMS Bulwark until the introduc", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17148", "17149", "17476", "17478"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The retirement of HMS Albion and Bulwark will not impact the operational programme of the Royal Marines, who continue to deploy globally. Both are currently held at lower readiness having not been to sea since 2023 and 2017 respectively. This Government i...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "RFA Argus: Amphibious Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17148", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17149", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17476", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17478", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746371, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17476", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the capability of Bay Class landing dock ships to fulfil the amphibious operational requirements in the absence of HMS Albion and HMS Bulwark until the i", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17148", "17149", "17477", "17478"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The retirement of HMS Albion and Bulwark will not impact the operational programme of the Royal Marines, who continue to deploy globally. Both are currently held at lower readiness having not been to sea since 2023 and 2017 respectively. This Government i...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Amphibious Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17148", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17149", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17477", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17478", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745986, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17149", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the retirement of HMS (a) Albion and (b) Bulwark on the capability of the armed forces.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["17148", "17476", "17477", "17478"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The retirement of HMS Albion and Bulwark will not impact the operational programme of the Royal Marines, who continue to deploy globally. Both are currently held at lower readiness having not been to sea since 2023 and 2017 respectively. This Government i...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Albion and HMS Bulwark", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17148", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17476", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17477", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17478", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745986", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745985, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17148", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the potential operational implications are of retiring HMS (a) Albion and (b) Bulwark in March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["17149", "17476", "17477", "17478"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The retirement of HMS Albion and Bulwark will not impact the operational programme of the Royal Marines, who continue to deploy globally. Both are currently held at lower readiness having not been to sea since 2023 and 2017 respectively. This Government i...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Albion and HMS Bulwark", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17149", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17476", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17477", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17478", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745985", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746692, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17755", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of proposed increases in stamp prices on (a) consumers and (b) businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4418, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government does not have a role in Royal Mail\u2019s commercial decisions, including the prices of stamps and other services. In setting its prices, Royal Mail must observe the regulatory framework set by Ofcom which imposes price controls, \u2018safeguard caps...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business and Consumers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746349, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17395", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Autumn Budget 2024 on the public bodies for which his Department is responsible.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4418, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "At Autumn Budget 2024 HM Treasury announced the funding settlement agreed for my department for 2024-25 and 2025-26. By working with HM Treasury we have ensured that the settlement provides the funding required for the public bodies, for which my departme...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Bodies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746349", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746101, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17228", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman's report on women\u2019s State Pension age changes, published on 21 March 2024, if she will publish related (a) impact assessments and (b) fin", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "We will consider what to publish when we announce our decision on the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman\u2019s report.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746232, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17269", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many thefts of motor vehicle from Network Rail owned car parks there were in each of the last five years; and how many of these resulted in a criminal prosecution.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "According to British Transport Police (BTP) data, there have been 68 thefts of motor vehicles at the 20 Network Rail managed stations between January 2020 and up to and including the 2nd December 2024. Of these, 5 have resulted in criminal prosecution. Ye...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Theft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746232", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746377, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17482", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the progress of (a) the Type 26 frigate programme and (b) its delivery schedule.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 483, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Ministry of Defence continues to work closely with BAE Systems (BAES) to ensure the Type 26 programme remains on track to meet all user requirements and deliver world-class Anti-Submarine Warfare (ASW) frigates to replace the Type 23. Following the re...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Type 26 Frigates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746377", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746100, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17227", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman's report on women\u2019s State Pension age changes, published on 21 March 2024, if she will publish the related departmental submissions to th", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "We will not publish the Departmental submissions to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman. The Parliamentary and Health Ombudsman\u2019s investigations are conducted in private as set out in section 7(2) of the Parliamentary Commissioner Act 1967.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746157, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17189", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2024 to Question 16211 on National Grid: Costs of the Western and Eastern Links, whether (a) he and (b) Ofgem is able to provide the estimate requested.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4998, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The analysis of an onshore reinforcement (i.e. overhead pylons) for Western Green Link was conducted 16 years ago and cost estimates for alternative options are not available.As the option of an onshore reinforcement for Eastern Green Link 1&amp;2 did not...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Grid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746321, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17286", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what proportion of complaints to the Trustmark scheme in relation to the Green Homes Grant scheme have been upheld; how much compensation has been paid to Green Homes Grant recipients due to ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5099, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The department does not hold the Trustmark complaint data regarding the Green Homes Grant Voucher Scheme.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Green Homes Grant Scheme: Complaints", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746321", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746323, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17287", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department has taken to (a) identify and (b) notify people who may have had spray foam installed through a Green Homes Grant about (i) potential damage caused by spray foam to ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5099, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Green Homes Grant Voucher Scheme required that consumers seek advice from a suitably qualified TrustMark registered installer before they applied for a voucher. It also required that installations meet Publicly Available Standard (PAS) 2035.If a homeo...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Insulation: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746323", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746326, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17288", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the (a) voucher approval, (b) issuance and (c) payment processes for the Green Homes Grant.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5099, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "An evaluation of the Green Homes Grant Voucher Scheme was published in November 2023 under the previous Government. It can be found on GOV.UK: www.gov.uk/government/publications/green-homes-grant-voucher-scheme-evaluation.Further evaluation of the scheme ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Green Homes Grant Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746326", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746327, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17289", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what data his Department holds on the number of homes that used Green Homes Grant vouchers for spray foam insulation.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5099, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "A breakdown of measures installed under the Green Homes Grant voucher scheme can be found in the Green Homes Grant evaluation report: www.gov.uk/government/publications/green-homes-grant-voucher-scheme-evaluation.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Insulation: Green Homes Grant Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746327", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746317, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the mean payment to each Government funded hospice was in each year since 2015.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746317", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746167, "askingMemberId": 4918, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17278", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to promote awareness of early symptoms of Parkinson's disease amongst GPs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parkinson's Disease: General Practitioners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746315, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17280", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much Government funding has been provided to hospices in each year since 2015.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746315", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746314, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17279", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospices there were in England in each year since 2015; and how many of those received Government funding in each of those years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746314", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746090, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17259", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of changes to the eligibility criteria for the Winter Fuel Payment on (a) primary care, (b) hospitals and (c) Pharmacy First.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Winter Fuel Allowance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746026, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17089", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with representatives of hospices since the Autumn Budget 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746026", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745973, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17192", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason the Connect to Work programme will be implemented in 2025, in the context of its predecessor programme being planned for 2024; and if she will make an estimate of the potential impact of", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4083, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "As announced in the Get Britain Working White Paper published 26 November 2024 Get Britain Working White Paper - GOV.UK, the new voluntary, locally led, supported employment programme Connect to Work will be the first programme under the Government\u2019s new ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Connect to Work", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745973", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746175, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17404", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.19 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October, if she will allocate funding to rebuild the B3191 between Watchet and Blue Anchor.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "At the Budget on 30 October, the Chancellor announced \u00a31.6 billion of capital funding for English local highway authorities for highway maintenance for the 2025/26 financial year, an increase of \u00a3500 million or nearly 50% compared to the current financial...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746247, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17429", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will take steps to (a) tackle the use of (i) bots and (ii) third-party resellers on the DVSA booking system and (b) ensure equitable access to driving tests.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "To ensure fairness for everyone wanting to book a practical driving test, the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency (DVSA) continues to work hard to combat the unscrupulous practice of reselling tests, very often at significant profit. DVSA deploys enhanced...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746247", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746158, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17343", "questionText": "What discussions she has had with car manufacturers on progress towards achieving the zero emission vehicle mandate for cars by 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "My Ministerial colleagues across Government and I meet regularly with vehicle manufacturers to discuss a wide range of issues including the transition to zero emission vehicles. We are working closely with the sector to ensure that British industry benefi...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Carbon Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745969, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17125", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding from the Spring Budget 2022 for the purchase of new electric vans via the plug-in vehicle grant remains available.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Over the last two financial years since Spring 2022, the Plug in Van Grant has supported the purchase over 30,000 zero emission vans. The Government continues to recognise the importance of grants, providing \u00a3120 million for next financial year to incenti...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Grants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745969", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746043, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17201", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has had discussions with representatives of the insurance industry on (a) increases in car insurance costs and (b) steps being taken by (i) the Government and (ii) insurers to reduce those costs.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government committed in its manifesto to tackle the high costs of motor insurance. To deliver on this commitment, the UK Government has formed a cross-government Taskforce on motor insurance, co-chaired by the Department for Transport and His Majesty...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Insurance: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746038, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17064", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason the Fire and Rescue Service is not receiving the exemption from the rise in National Insurance contributions as the other Emergency Services.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "To repair the public finances and help raise the revenue required to fund public services, the Government has taken the difficult decision to increase employer National Insurance. The Government will provide support for public sector employers, including ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fire and Rescue Services: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746042, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17200", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment of the adequacy of the affordability of insurance for (a) young and (b) all drivers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government committed in its manifesto to tackle the high costs of motor insurance. To deliver on this commitment, the UK Government has formed a cross-government Taskforce on motor insurance, co-chaired by the Department for Transport and His Majesty...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Insurance: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746104, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17087", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to increase the availability of practical driving tests in Gosport constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency\u2019s (DVSA\u2019s) main priority is to reduce car practical driving test waiting times, whilst upholding road safety standards. Measures in place to reduce waiting times for customers at all driving test centres (DTC), incl...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: Gosport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746141, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17091", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Autumn Budget 2024 on the (a) number of family businesses and (b) employment levels within those businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government inherited a difficult fiscal situation and so we are asking businesses to contribute to fixing the foundations and our public services. As part of the decisions made at Budget, the Government assessed the impact of measures introduced on bu...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746150, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17078", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will hold discussions with the BBC on (a) breaches of a broadcasting licence and (b) other matters raised in the report by Ofcom entitled Annual Report on the BBC 2023-2024, published on 2", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4607, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The BBC has a duty to reflect, represent and serve the diverse communities of all of the United Kingdom\u2019s nations and regions. We want it to reflect the full diversity of people, communities and experiences across the UK so that more people can see and he...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "BBC", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746088, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17257", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of changes in liability for inheritance tax on levels of tax avoidance.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "At Autumn Budget 2024, the Government took a number of difficult but necessary decisions on tax, welfare, and spending to restore economic stability, fix the public finances, and support public services. These were tough decisions given the situation we i...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inheritance Tax: Tax Avoidance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746088", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746392, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17496", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of ensuring future housing developments provide electronic vehicle charging facilities for residents.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Since June 2022, Part S of Schedule 1 to the Building Regulations 2010 requires new residential properties with associated parking to have access to electric vehicle chargepoints.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Charging Points", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746392", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746499, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17585", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to increase the availability of driving tests in Slough constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency\u2019s (DVSA) main priority is upholding road safety standards while it works hard to reduce car practical driving test waiting times. Measures in place to reduce waiting times for customers at all driving test centres (...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: Slough", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746362, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17469", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her oral statement on Border Security and Asylum of 22 July 2024, Official Report, column 384, what assessment her Department has made of the cost effectiveness of (a) Campsfield Hou", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17467", "17468"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Detention plays a key role in maintaining effective immigration controls and securing the UK\u2019s borders, particularly in connection with the removal of people who have no right to remain in the UK but who refuse to leave voluntarily. The immigration remova...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Campsfield House Immigration Removal Centre", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17467", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17468", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746362", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746361, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17468", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2024 to Question 15154 on Campsfield House Immigration Removal Centre, what review process was undertaken by her Department on the commercial agreement with Galli", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17467", "17469"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Detention plays a key role in maintaining effective immigration controls and securing the UK\u2019s borders, particularly in connection with the removal of people who have no right to remain in the UK but who refuse to leave voluntarily. The immigration remova...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Campsfield House Immigration Removal Centre", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17467", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17469", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746361", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746360, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17467", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2024 to Question 15050 on Campsfield House Immigration Removal Centre, what assessment her Department has made of the cost-effectiveness of (a) Campsfield House a", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17468", "17469"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Detention plays a key role in maintaining effective immigration controls and securing the UK\u2019s borders, particularly in connection with the removal of people who have no right to remain in the UK but who refuse to leave voluntarily. The immigration remova...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration Removal Centres", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17468", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "17469", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746360", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746152, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17080", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many hotels are being used for the provision of accommodation for asylum seekers in Northern Ireland; and if she will make an estimate of the number of hotels that will be required by 31 December ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Home Office has a statutory obligation to provide destitute asylum seekers with accommodation and subsistence support whilst their application for asylum is being considered.The Home Office does not publish data on the number of hotels in use. However...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746318, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17378", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of her Department's staff have transferred from Work Coach roles to roles assisting irregular migrants with benefits claims.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4979, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Irregular migrants cannot access public funds benefits. To access public funds benefits, individuals are required to hold an immigration status which does not prevent them from accessing public funds, which irregular migrants will not hold. Since irregula...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746318", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746341, "askingMemberId": 5120, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17340", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Department for Culture, Media and Sport's response to the Government's consultation on the structure, distribution and governance of the statutory levy on gambling operators, published on ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4125, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Within schools, statutory relationships, sex and health education (RSHE) supports children and young people to make informed decisions in relation to their mental wellbeing and online behaviour. The RSHE statutory guidance is clear that children and young...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gambling: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746341", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746289, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17383", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average (a) primary and (b) secondary school class size was in (i) Mid Cheshire constituency, (ii) Cheshire and (iii) England in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4125, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The department publishes annual statistics on class sizes in state-funded schools in England here: https://explore-education-statistics.service.gov.uk/find-statistics/school-pupils-and-their-characteristics. The England averages for the most recent five y...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Class Sizes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746298, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17385", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average per-pupil funding was that her Department allocated to (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in (i) Mid Cheshire constituency, (ii) Cheshire and (iii) England in each year since 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17384"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4125, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The department cannot provide comparable funding back to 2010 due to the changes in the funding system since that time. The scope of the per pupil funding before and after the 2018/19 financial year are not directly comparable. In particular, funding for ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupils: Per Capita Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17384", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746291, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17384", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department allocated to (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in (i) Mid Cheshire constituency, (ii) Cheshire and (iii) England in each of the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17385"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4125, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The department cannot provide comparable funding back to 2010 due to the changes in the funding system since that time. The scope of the per pupil funding before and after the 2018/19 financial year are not directly comparable. In particular, funding for ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17385", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746355, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17326", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2024 to Question 16677 on Community Policing: Cambridgeshire, how many of the 13,000 additional police officers Cambridgeshire Constabulary will receive.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1533, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "As part of the Government\u2019s Safer Streets mission, the Home Secretary has made a clear commitment to strengthen neighbourhood policing through the introduction of a Neighbourhood Policing Guarantee.This includes delivering an additional 13,000 police offi...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Policing: Cambridgeshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746355", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745960, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17194", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sports, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the Design and Artists Copyright Society\u2019s report entitled, UK Visual Artists a survey of earnings and contracts, p", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1446, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "My department has made no recent assessment of the potential impact of digital copying on artists' and performers' remuneration. However, the Government wants to see remuneration arrangements that create the right conditions for sparking and driving innov...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arts: Copyright", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745960", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746126, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17143", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the total cost to the public purse of out of court settlements for employment tribunal cases across local government in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4569, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The information requested is not held centrally.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Tribunals Service: Local Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746189, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17396", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2024 to Question 15348 on Gatwick Airport: Noise, what measures the Aviation Night Noise Effects study will use to investigate the potential impact of flight noise on child", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4316, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Aviation Night Noise Effects study has been developed to examine the relationship between exposure to night-time aviation noise and sleep disturbance and annoyance in adults and has not been designed to investigate effects on children.  ", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gatwick Airport: Noise", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746153, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17185", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Strategic Defence Review will be (a) delivered to Ministers and (b) made available to the public.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "As previously announced by the Secretary of State for Defence to the House of Commons, the Reviewers will make their final report to the Prime Minister, Chancellor of the Exchequer and Secretary of State for Defence in the Spring of 2025. The Secretary of...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Strategic Defence Review", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746151, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17079", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what benefits would a successful applicant for Pension Credit potentially be eligible for in addition to the Winter Fuel Payment.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4077, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "In addition to the Winter Fuel Payment, Pension Credit provides access to a number of other benefits and support including: o help with rent via Housing Benefit;o a Council Tax reduction;o Cold Weather Payments and other help from the Social Fund includin...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit: Social Security Benefits", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746214, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17421", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if his Department will make an assessment of the adequacy of the Fireworks Regulations 2004 at protecting (a) people and (b) animals from the negative impacts of fireworks.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4418, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Most people use fireworks in a responsible, safe, and appropriate manner and there are laws in place to address situations where fireworks are misused. The current regulatory framework is designed to support people to enjoy fireworks whilst lowering the r...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fireworks: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746138, "askingMemberId": 4521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17190", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training is available through the medium of Welsh for probation officers\u00a0in\u00a0Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4056, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Currently, whilst we do not offer national training for Probation Officers in Welsh we can provide learning materials and effective practice briefings in Welsh upon request.We are dedicated to fostering a workplace environment that encourages and embraces...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Probation Service: Welsh Language", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746336, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17398", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if her Department will take steps to help local authorities speed-up the processing of blue badges.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department for Transport sets the legislation that governs the Blue Badge scheme and provides guidance for local authorities who are solely responsible for administering the scheme, including issuing the badges. There are no timescales set for adminis...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blue Badge Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746336", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746149, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17077", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of stopped vehicle detection technology on motorways.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "We recognise the importance of technology working to support our road users and that is why the Department commissioned the Office of Rail and Road (ORR) to undertake an independent review of the effectiveness of technology on smart motorways, including s...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motorways: ICT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746356, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17273", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make it her policy to not include hybrid cars in the 2030 phase-out of vehicles with internal combustion engines.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The commitment to restore the 2030 phase-out date for new cars with internal combustion engines has always meant that some hybrids will be allowed until 2035, when all new cars will be required to be zero emission. Further details will be set out in the u...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746356", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746281, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17331", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information her Department holds on the number of delayed services on the Bedford Line in (a) Q3 and (b) Q4 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": " Information relating to the number of delayed services on the Bedford line is not held by the department. The Office of Rail and Road (ORR) publishes quarterly statistics on punctuality and reliability for passenger trains in Great Britain at: https://da...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Thameslink Line: Bedford", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746385, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17463", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of restricting the use of treble barbed fishhooks in England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4382, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The use of barbed hooks is currently restricted by several byelaws covering specific fisheries in areas throughout England and Wales. The suitability and need for these restrictions will continue to be monitored and may inform changes if appropriate, howe...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fish: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746385", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746035, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17232", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2024 to Question 6534 on Land Drainage: Property Development, whether he (a) has made and (b) plans to make an assessment of the potential regulato", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4645, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "A full regulatory impact assessment, including consideration of costs and benefits, would be prepared as part of any implementation of Schedule 3 to the Flood and Water Management Act 2010. No such assessment is available at this stage.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Land Drainage: Property Development", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746035", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746387, "askingMemberId": 5342, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17466", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce air pollution levels in Ashbourne, in the context of the establishment of an air quality management area following elevated levels of", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4645, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "When an Air quality management area (AGMA) is declared, local authorities are required to produce an Air Quality Action Plan (AQAP) to bring air pollution down to within statutory limits. Defra has been engaging with Derbyshire Dales District Council to e...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Ashbourne", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746387", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746170, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17402", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the (a) adequacy of regulations on the fishing of bass by charter boats which are also commercially-registered fishing vessels and (b) potential merits", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4382, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Bass Fisheries Management Plan published in December 2023 sets out a number goals and measures to deliver long-term sustainable management of bass fisheries in English and Welsh waters. This includes working with the newly established bass management ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sea Bass: Quotas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746206, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17351", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a timebound legal duty to end overfishing in UK waters.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4382, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Fisheries Act 2020 contains a commitment to recover stocks to sustainable levels through the development of Fisheries Management Plans (FMPs). We are taking this approach having learned from the well-intentioned but ultimately unachievable single dead...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fishing Catches", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746163, "askingMemberId": 4918, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17274", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his strategy for NHS workforce planning, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of shortages in the number of clinicians specialising in neurology on the adequacy o", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Currently, there are no specific plans to make an assessment of the potential impact of shortages in the number of clinicians specialising in neurology on the adequacy of care for patients with Parkinson's disease or other neurological conditions.As of Ju...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Neurological Diseases: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746357, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure (a) transparency and (b) accountability in dairy supply chains.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4382, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Defra is committed to delivering this Government\u2019s ambition to support British farmers to boost Britain\u2019s food security. Central to achieving this ambition will be pursuing the right approach to fairness across the supply chain. The Fair Dealing Obligatio...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dairy Farming", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746357", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746358, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to publish a consultation on potential changes to the Fair Dealing Obligations (Milk) Regulations 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4382, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Defra is committed to enhancing fairness across supply chains, which will support farmers to boost Britain\u2019s food security. The Fair Dealing Obligations (Milk) Regulations (2024), which were introduced earlier this year, represent an important step forwar...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Milk", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746358", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746320, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17285", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he will take steps to provide redress to people whose (a) property values or (b) access to mortgage finance has been impacted by spray foam insulation installed using a Green Homes Gr", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5099, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department has worked with the insulation industry and lending community to address concerns relating to spray foam. Protocols were published in March 2023 to support surveyors to assess spray foam, provide reassurance to lenders, and inform consumers...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Insulation: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746320", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746148, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17209", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she plans to publish a sexual harassment survey.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4657, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Office for Equality and Opportunity plans to strengthen protections against workplace sexual harassment through the Employment Rights Bill. These measures intend to amend the Equality Act 2010 to:\u25cf require employers to take \u201call reasonable steps\u201d to p...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sexual Harassment: Surveys", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746364, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17465", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funds the Government has committed to veterans charities\u00a0in each of the\u00a0last\u00a0two\u00a0years; and how much each such charity has received.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5235, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The information is not held in the format requested. Information held by the Ministry of Defence (MOD) does not differentiate between veterans\u2019 charities; charities that generally support the Armed Forces community including veterans; and charities that h...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Charities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746364", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746156, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17188", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he received the External Scrutiny Team Report 2024 into the Reserves as referred to in Section 113a of the Reserve Forces Act 1996; and whether he plans to publish his response.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5235, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "My right hon. Friend the Secretary of State for Defence received the External Scrutiny Team\u2019s 2024 report on 29 July 2024. We are most grateful to the team for their work. The Ministry of Defence will place their 2024 report in the Library of the House in...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Reserve Forces", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746155, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17187", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to commission a Women\u2019s Veterans Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5235, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government will always stand up for those who have served our country, and I am leading work across Government and with civil society to look at the best ways to ensure all veterans get access to the support and opportunities they need and deserve. W...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746124, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17141", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to ensure that support is available for households that (a) are not on low incomes and (b) do not have access to capital upfront to retrofit their homes.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5099, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "As part of the Warm Homes Plan, the Government has committed an initial \u00a33.4 billion over the next 3 years towards heat decarbonisation and household energy efficiency, with \u00a31 billion of this allocated to next year. Additional funding will be considered ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746363, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17464", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of his Department's (a) computers, (b) laptops, (c) phones and (d) USB sticks were (i) lost and (ii) stolen in each month in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 483, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The table below shows the number of computers, laptops, phones and USB sticks which were either lost or stolen in each month in 2023.DateComputersLaptopsUSBsPhonesJan-2301329Feb-2301003Mar-23038210Apr-2301003May-230828Jun-23010112Jul-230968Aug-2305139Sep-...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: ICT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746363", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746127, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17144", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the total cost to the public purse of out of court settlements for employment tribunal cases across the NHS in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "This information is not held centrally by the Department or NHS England. No estimate has been made on the total cost to the public purse of out of court settlements for employment tribunal cases across the National Health Service in the last five years.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Employment Tribunals Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746165, "askingMemberId": 4918, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17276", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of consultants specialising in the treatment of Parkinson's disease required to meet current needs of patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17275"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "We have launched a 10-Year Health Plan to reform the National Health Service. A central and core part of the plan will be our workforce and how we ensure we train and provide the staff, technology, and infrastructure the NHS needs to care for patients acr...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parkinson's Disease: Consultants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17275", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746164, "askingMemberId": 4918, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17275", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to encourage students to take up careers in neurology.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["17276"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "We have launched a 10-Year Health Plan to reform the National Health Service. A central and core part of the plan will be our workforce and how we ensure we train and provide the staff, technology, and infrastructure the NHS needs to care for patients acr...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Neurology: Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "17276", "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746253, "askingMemberId": 4846, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17266", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she has had discussions with the Minister for Justice in Northern Ireland on creating a criminal offence of drink spiking.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4849, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Spiking is already an offence in England and Wales and Northern Ireland. We are, however, currently working across Government on a proposed new offence covering spiking, which has included discussions, at official level, with the Department of Justice (No...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Spiking: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746253", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747438, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18341", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to support people who do not qualify for council funding and are (a) homeless and (b) at risk of homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747347, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18340", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of her planned ticket pricing policies on (a) affordability and (b) ridership for passengers using the C2C train routes in the period after its re", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747347", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747345, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18339", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department plans to take to (a) establish and (b) monitor (i) customer service and (ii) other performance standards on the C2C train routes when they are under public ownership.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747345", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747344, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18338", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has allocated funding for step-free access improvements at stations on C2C routes.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747344", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747342, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18337", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of planned funding for (a) services and (b) infrastructure on C2C train routes in the period following its re-nationalisation.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747342", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747348, "askingMemberId": 5360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18336", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the press notice entitled \u00a37 million to tackle antisemitism in education confirmed, published by her Department on 7 October 2024, how her Department plans to use this funding in (a) Hendon an", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747348", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747316, "askingMemberId": 5360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18335", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to support leaseholders with rises in (a) ground rent, (b) service charges and (c) building insurance in Hendon.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747316", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747304, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18334", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an estimate of the number of e-passports that do not work at UK airports; and what steps she is taking to help resolve that issue.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747503, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18333", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to tackle extreme flooding in (a) Tewkesbury constituency and (b) rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747500, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18332", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of proposed changes to inheritance tax on (a) small family farm closures and (b) internal food production security", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747498, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18331", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will take steps to ensure that additional funding for Special Educational Needs and Disabilities in mainstream schools is equitably distributed in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747497, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18330", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to (a) help tackle anti-social behaviour and (b) cooperate with the police in communities that host large-scale sporting events other than football.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747496, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure animal welfare standards are (a) observed and (b) reviewed in the horse racing industry.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747362, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of sourcing military uniforms from China.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747362", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747490, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18327", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of allowing hon. Members to propose locations for funding from the Road Safety Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747485, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18326", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of financial support for people paying increased water bills in the South West.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747484, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral contribution of 24 November 2024 by the then Secretary of State for Transport, Official Report column 369, when the road safety strategy will be implemented.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747483, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18324", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of a graded junction at the A30 Plusha junction.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747381, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18323", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many net additional full time equivalent roles will be required to staff the Military Strategic Headquarters; and at what cost.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747381", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747380, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18322", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the condition of (a) former UK military sites and (b) monuments of registered historic importance in Hong Kong.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747380", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747379, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18321", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department\u2019s policy is on reporting Unidentified Aerial Phenomena; and whether new material has been classified on the subject since the UK\u2019s declassification programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747379", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747378, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18320", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department's artificial intelligence software is Defence Writing compatible.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747378", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747377, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18319", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what priorities on what timelines he has issued to the National Resilience Academy.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747377", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747376, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18318", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has had discussions with Cabinet colleagues on (a) transporting and (b) housing illegal migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747376", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747375, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18317", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the scale of Other Ranks regularly declining use of official catering facilities on camp.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747375", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747374, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18316", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July to Question 189 on Defence, what steps he is taking to consult widely with (a) serving personnel and (b) veterans.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747374", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747373, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18315", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Answer of 26 July to Question 198 on Defence, what the cost to date of the Strategic Defence Review is (a) in total and (b) by category of allowance or expenditure.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747373", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747372, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18314", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2024 to Question 8456 on Strategic Defence Review, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the interpretation of recommendations relating to the use of artificial intel", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747371, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18313", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2024 to Question 8456 on Strategic Defence Review, if he will redraft guidelines on (a) submissions, (b) the use of executive summaries and (c) bullet pointed-recommendations ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747368, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18312", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2024 to Question 8456 on Strategic Defence Review, whether the artificial intelligence software being used to assess responses to the Strategic Defence Review was sourced from", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747368", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747366, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18311", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the planners of the Strategic Defence Review were notified of the intention to retire (a) HMS Albion, (b) HMS Bulwark and (c) other assets.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747366", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747320, "askingMemberId": 5344, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18310", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many times UK ambassadors have met Organisations of Persons with Disabilities in the past year.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747320", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747305, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-16T00:00:00", "uin": "18309", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of the monthly payment of war pensions.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747305", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747361, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18308", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the National Insurance contributions rise on the provision of fast-track care to patients applying for Continuing Healthcare fundi", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747361", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747461, "askingMemberId": 5324, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18307", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he plans to implement the provisions of the Neonatal Care (Leave and Pay) Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747461", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747308, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18306", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will include section 17(5) of the Environment Act 2021 in the Green Book.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747308", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747307, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18305", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to update the Water Supply (Water Quality) Regulations 2016.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747307", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747306, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18304", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to consult on Part G of the building regulations to improve water efficiency standards.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747306", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747494, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions there have been under the Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities Involving Animals) (England) (Amendment) Regulations 2019.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747495, "askingMemberId": 5302, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-12T00:00:00", "uin": "18302", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to ensure that the National Wealth Fund is equipped to provide offtake finance and hedging instruments for the critical minerals industry.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747357, "askingMemberId": 5291, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-12T00:00:00", "uin": "18301", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the potential merits of including long covid as an industrial illness for people working the NHS during the covid-19 pandemic.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747357", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747296, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18300", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding her Department plans to provide for rail infrastructure in Wales in each of the next three financial years; and whether she has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of increasing th", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747402, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-16T00:00:00", "uin": "18299", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the National Security Unit for Procurement plans to publish guidance for contracting authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747402", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747333, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18298", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing additional funding to local authorities to support them to meet their statutory homelessness duties effectivel", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747333", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747319, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he plans to take to support (a) veterans and (b) bereaved service families in Northern Ireland, in the context of the closure of the Veterans' Support Office.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747319", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747341, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16662 on NHS: Public Consultation, what the budget is for deliberative engagement by type of spend in the 2024-25 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747341", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747340, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of changes to employer National Insurance contributions at the Autumn Budget 2024 on children's hospices.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747340", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747414, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18294", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of legislation on tackling (a) tax evasion and (b) illicit financial transactions in British Overseas Territories; and what esti", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747414", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747398, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to implement the recommendations within the Blood Cancer UK report entitled, UK Blood Cancer Action Plan, published on 4 September 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747398", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747369, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18292", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an estimate of the potential impact of freezing Income Tax thresholds until 2028 on the number of people who will begin paying (a) Income Tax and (b) the higher rate of Income Tax in each financial ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747369", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747419, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the amount of social housing available for families in need of housing support who need four or more bedrooms.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747419", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747297, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18290", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will review the issuing of licenses to export endangered European eels.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747394, "askingMemberId": 5240, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18289", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure staff receive training on the Scottish benefits system.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747394", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747358, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18288", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has determined the appropriateness of central recovery support following flooding in Chippenham after Storm Berk.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747358", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747356, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18287", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions she has had with the Minister for Water and Flooding following her visit to Chippenham on 26 November 2024; and if she will publish a note of those discussions.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747356", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747355, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18286", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 16051 on Storms: Disaster Relief, how she defines exceptional.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747355", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747280, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18285", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of rape trial waiting times on people who have made allegations of rape.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747351, "askingMemberId": 5216, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18284", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the funding for local authorities to provide drug and alcohol support services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747351", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747313, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2024 to Question 12587 on Breast Cancer: Nurses, whether his Department's plans to train clinical cancer staff will be included in the (a) forthcoming NHS ten-", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747313", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747312, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2024 to Question 12590 on Breast Cancer: Genetics, what steps his Department is taking to reduce regional inequities in access to genetic counselling.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747312", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747311, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on (a) improving the process for clinical trials and (b) ensuring that those trials are more accessible for teenagers and young adults.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747311", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747310, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18280", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that young people with cancer have equity of access to age-appropriate, specialist psychological support in the Buckinghamshire, Oxfordshire, Berkshire West Integr", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747310", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747309, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18279", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for the (a) diagnosis and (b) treatment of cancer in teenagers and young adults in the Buckinghamshire, Oxfordshire and West Berkshire Integrated Car", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747309", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747493, "askingMemberId": 5197, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18278", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when her Department was informed that former employees of (a) ISG and (b) ESS had access to the layout of prison estates; for what reason former employees were able to access the plans following the cessation of ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747329, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18277", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information her Department holds on the number of applications for exemption to allow civilian cargo planes that are (a) destined for Israel and (b) transporting munitions of war to overfly British soverei", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747329", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747295, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18276", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether Herzi Halevi was given special mission diplomatic immunity to visit the UK in November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747382, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18275", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the (a) adequacy of the condition of the canal towpath network and (b) potential merits of enabling higher levels of use of the canal towpath network for (i) walking and (ii) cyc", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747382", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747352, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18274", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how the National Wealth Fund will support developing port capacity.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747352", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747300, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18273", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what is the net change in prison places since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747300", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747327, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18272", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many sound moderators are held on firearms certificates.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747327", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747326, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18271", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the (a) effectiveness and (b) efficiency of the National Firearms Licensing Management System; and whether her Department plans to update the system.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747326", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747325, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18270", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number and proportion of GPs who have downloaded the IT update to allow the placement of markers on the medical notes of firearms certificate holders.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747325", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747324, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18269", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to require General Practitioners to place a marker on the medical notes of firearms certificate holders.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747324", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747323, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18268", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has had meetings with representatives of (a) police, (b) gun control groups, (c) British Shooting Sports Council and (d) British Association for Shooting and Conservation to discuss firear", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747323", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747509, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18267", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department's statistics entitled Social housing lettings in England, tenancies: April 2023 to March 2024, published on 5 December 2024, if she will breakdow", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747502, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18266", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department's statistics on Social housing lettings in England, April 2023 to March 2024, published on 5 December 2024, if she will make an estimate of the n", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747501, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18265", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department's statistics on Social housing lettings in England, April 2023 to March 2024, published on 5 December 2024, whether her Department is taking step", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747499, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18264", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department's statistics entitled Social housing lettings in England, tenancies: April 2023 to March 2024, published on 5 December 2024, if she will make an ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747447, "askingMemberId": 5151, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18263", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking through the Youth Guarantee to support care leavers at risk of dropping out of (a) education and (b) training.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747315, "askingMemberId": 5151, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18262", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the potential impact of workforce shortages in the early years sector on pre-school children\u2019s language and communication development.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747315", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747314, "askingMemberId": 5151, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18261", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support (a) language and (b) communication skills of children under three.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747314", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747515, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18260", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will meet with online consumers in Northern Ireland experiencing difficulties buying goods from Great Britain.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747514, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18259", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the impact of the General Product Safety Regulations on the ability of consumers in Northern Ireland to buy goods from Great Britain.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747513, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18258", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business and Trade on the potential impact of the General Product Safety Regulations 2023 on the ability of consumers in Northern Ireland to bu", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747525, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18257", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 16304 on Pension Credit: South Derbyshire, how many pensioner households in receipt of Housing Benefit and identified as potentially entitled to but", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747299, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18256", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make it his policy to retain the Acoustic Fish Deterrent aspect of the Development Consent Order to the Hinkley Point C (Nuclear Generating Station) Order 2013.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747299", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747487, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18255", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to (a) increase awareness and (b) raise the status with (i) universities and (ii) employers of the Level 3 Core Maths qualification.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747486, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18254", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of encouraging the Joint Council for Qualifications to include the Level 3 Core Maths qualification within the A level and Level 3 results documents to", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747350, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18253", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support the education of pupils at non-academised sixth forms in the context of planned industrial action.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747350", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747338, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18252", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will undertake a review of further education funding, in the context of the pay dispute with teachers at non-academised sixth forms.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747338", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747337, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-16T00:00:00", "uin": "18251", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to help resolve pay disputes with non-academised sixth forms who were not included in the 5.5% pay award announced for teachers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747337", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747353, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18250", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the support available to people who have left coercive relationships but continue to be subject to attempts at (a) financial and (b) other control by thei", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747353", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747451, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18249", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has made an estimate of the cost of nationalising the British Steel plant in Scunthorpe.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747449, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18248", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department has assessed the potential merits of nationalising the British Steel plant in Scunthorpe during its negotiations on that matter.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747489, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18247", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the UK Shared Prosperity Funding allocation will be for Lancashire County Council for the 2024/25 tax year.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747488, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18246", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the UK Shared Prosperity Funding allocation will be for Wyre Borough Council for the 2024/25 tax year.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747435, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18245", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the UK Shared Prosperity Funding allocation will be for Fylde Borough Council for the 2024/25 tax year.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747399, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18244", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many full-time-equivalent civil servants are working on the short-term let registration scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747399", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747360, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18243", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many full-time equivalent civil servants are working on the Dawlish Rail resilience programme.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747360", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747359, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18242", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to announce the allocation by local authority for the \u00a3740 million of SEND funding.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747359", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747318, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18241", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has issued to sixth form academies on securing capital funding for new school buildings when existing buildings are no longer fit for purpose.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747318", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747512, "askingMemberId": 5065, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18240", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2024 to Question 15335 on High Speed 2 Line: Complaints, how HS2 Ltd differentiates between enquiries and complaints; and how enquiries are escalated to complaints.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747349, "askingMemberId": 5060, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18239", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to reduce firework misuse in Makerfield constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747349", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747332, "askingMemberId": 5031, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18238", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the NHS supply of Futibatinib.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747332", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747331, "askingMemberId": 5031, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18237", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding is available for patients to receive the immunotherapy drug Futibatinib through the NHS; and what criteria his Department uses to determine whether a patient is eligible for any fundin", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747331", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747437, "askingMemberId": 5025, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-16T00:00:00", "uin": "18236", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to review the impact of alcohol on mental health..", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747418, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18235", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the level of support available to domestic abuse victims and their children in the Family Court system.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747418", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747520, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18234", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of her Department's regional office closures on (a) staff who are unable to relocate and (b) all staff.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747412, "askingMemberId": 4861, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18233", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent (a) meetings and (b) other discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on proposed changes to (a) Agricultural and (b) Business Property Relief.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747412", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747411, "askingMemberId": 4861, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18232", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings he has had with the (a) National Farmers Union, (b) Country Land and Business Association, (c) Countryside Alliance and (d) Central Association for Agricultural Valuers s", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747411", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747410, "askingMemberId": 4861, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18231", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many meetings he had with the (a) National Farmers' Union, (b) Country Land and Business Association, (c) Countryside Alliance and (d) Central Association for Agricultural Valuers ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747410", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747441, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18230", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of fires caused by batteries in electric bikes.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747439, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18229", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information her Department holds on\u00a0the number of fires as a result of batteries in electric bikes reported to emergency services.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747400, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18228", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of extending deemed reseller rules to cover UK-established sellers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747400", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747413, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18227", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of the report by Amnesty International entitled You feel like you are subhuman: Israel\u2019s genocide", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747413", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747510, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18226", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on (a) exemptions for and (b) flexibility in (i) sponsored visa and (ii) skilled workers visa guidance staff in her Depar", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747508, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-12T00:00:00", "uin": "18225", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish (a) staff turnover, (b) the number of new recruits and (c) the number of vacancies in her Department in each of the last three months.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747507, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-12T00:00:00", "uin": "18224", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in her Department are required to pay the NHS Health Surcharge.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747506, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-12T00:00:00", "uin": "18223", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in which of her Department's offices there are staff employed on sponsored visas who will not meet the salary threshold at the end of the current visa term.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747505, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-12T00:00:00", "uin": "18222", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in her Department are on sponsored visas; and how many will not meet the skilled worker visa salary threshold at the end of their visa term.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747523, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18221", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the implications for the Government's policies on departmental check-off arrangements of Supreme Court judgment [2024] UKSC 41 relating to (a) Secretary of State for the Department", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747522, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18220", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the press release entitled Conclusion of His Majesty the King\u2019s free portrait scheme, published on 28 November 2024, which local authorities did not request a portrait, excluding town and paris", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747521, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18219", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Conclusion of His Majesty The King\u2019s free Portrait Scheme, published on 28 November 2024, if he will list each (a) UK, (b) Welsh and (c) Scottish Governm", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747482, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18218", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Ministers are required to declare (a) spent and (b) unspent criminal convictions when they are formally appointed.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747481, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18217", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of variations in practice on the publication of Government Procurement Card and Electronic Purchasing Card transaction data by Governm", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747480, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18216", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has organised away days for Senior Civil Service officials since the dissolution of Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747479, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18215", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Civil Service Jobs advertisement reference 378636, why four positions are being recruited; whether they are new positions; and whether the former incumbents left since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747478, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18214", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether there are plans for 10 Downing Street to communicate via the Blue Sky social media channel.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747477, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18213", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, whether he has a policy on appointing Ministers of the Crown with (a) spent and (b) unspent criminal convictions.", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747476, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18212", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, how many special advisers in 10 Downing Street cover foreign affairs.", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747475, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18211", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, whether members of the Lobby may take photographs on flights travelling with the Prime Minister.", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747474, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18210", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, when Sue Gray's employment as a special adviser ended.", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747473, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18209", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans she has to amend the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747472, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18208", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, when he became aware of the previous fraud conviction of the former Transport Secretary, the Rt Hon. Member for Sheffield Heeley.", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747470, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18207", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will publish the (a) environmental principles and (b) equalities impact assessment for the Chagos Islands handover decision.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747469, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18206", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions he has had with (a) representatives of the British Museum and (b) the Greek government on the Elgin Marbles.", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747467, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18205", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to his oral contribution of 4 December 2024, Official Report, column 291, on what evidential basis he stated that two of the Leader of the Opposition\u2019s predecessors had convictions for breaking covid rules.", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747467", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747465, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18204", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, what information he holds on how many Ministers have criminal convictions.", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747464, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18203", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans to publish his tax return on gov.uk for 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747464", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747301, "askingMemberId": 4806, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18202", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate he has made of carbon prices in 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747301", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747294, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18201", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2024 to Question 12975 on Department for Transport: Data Processing, what the operational scope is of her Department's Organisational AI programme; and which Departmental a", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747293, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18200", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2024 to Question 13063 on High Speed 2 Line: Construction, what information her Department holds on levels of compliance by contractors with the HS2 Environmental Minimum R", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747292, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18199", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what penalties can be applied to rail operators for failure to provide adequate support for disabled passengers to access train services; and whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of introd", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747291, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18198", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the planned timetable is for opening (a) Bedlington, (b) Blyth Bebside and (c) Northumberland Park station on the Northumberland Line.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747290, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18197", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the planned timetable is for reopening the Northumberland Line between Newcastle and Ashington.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747289, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18196", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make it her policy to ensure that cash payment remains an option for rail passengers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747288, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18195", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps National Rail is taking to ensure the adequacy of cyber security at train stations.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747287, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18194", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans she has for the future of rolling stock leasing agreements.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747286, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18193", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the proposed expansion of Stansted airport on regional airports.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747285, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18192", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has (a) met and (b) had discussions with her counterpart in Scotland since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747284, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18191", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions (a) she and (b) her predecessor has had with her counterpart in the Welsh government since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747283, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18190", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information her Department holds on the number of people who have made journeys using the \u00a32 cap on bus fares.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747282, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18189", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department is taking steps to use rail freight to help support the building of new homes.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747281, "askingMemberId": 4798, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18188", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department plans to provide additional funding to publicly-owned rail operators for the cost of changes to employer National Insurance contributions made at the Autumn Budget 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747504, "askingMemberId": 4780, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18187", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many trusts submitted grant applications for the Trust Capacity Fund in the most recent funding window.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747518, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18186", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to stop third party discrimination.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747517, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18185", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to tackle sexual harassment in the workplace.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747516, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18184", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department has a gender action plan.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747354, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18183", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many fines for school absence were issued to the parents of neurodiverse children who missed school for a reason relating to their condition in the last 12 months; and if she will make an assessment of the ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747354", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747330, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18182", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of material switching by food producers currently using metal food cans on (a) UK food security and (b) the (i) recyclability of a", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747330", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747420, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18181", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department is taking steps to help support farmers to receive higher prices for their produce.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747420", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747343, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18180", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of temporary accommodation on the (a) mental and (b) physical health of families in that accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747343", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747339, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18179", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy that health visitors should make routine visits to families with babies that are living in temporary accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747339", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747336, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18178", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of temporary accommodation on the mental health of children within that accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747336", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747335, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18177", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on what the (a) most common illnesses and (b) incidence of each of those illnesses experienced by babies and children in temporary accommodation were in the la", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747335", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747492, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18176", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will take steps to increase resources for enforcement agencies to (a) investigate and (b) prosecute complex sanctions evasion schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747491, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18175", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of allocating confiscated proceeds from (a) sanctions breaches and (b) penalties for (i) human rights and (ii) humanitar", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747322, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18174", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to provide transition pathways for oil and gas workers.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747322", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747524, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18173", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she plans to take to tackle money laundering through cryptocurrencies, in the context of the National Crime Agency's Operation Destabilise investigations.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747462, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18172", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of the harms of (a) drug and (b) alcohol misuse.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747452, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18171", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to ensure the availability of rehabilitation treatment for people with (a) drug and (b) alcohol dependencies in (i) Slough constituency and (ii) Berkshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747445, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18170", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps this Department is taking to reduce (a) drug- and (b) alcohol-related deaths.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747417, "askingMemberId": 4637, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18169", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend copyright legislation in relation to text and data mining.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747417", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747416, "askingMemberId": 4637, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18168", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of re-establishing the Cultural Renewal taskforce.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747416", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747415, "askingMemberId": 4637, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18167", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of reviewing the curriculum framework for primary school science as part of her Department\u2019s curriculum review.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747415", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747519, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18166", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October to Question 6418 on Further Education: VAT, for what reason further education colleges do not meet the rationale for admission to either refund scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747446, "askingMemberId": 4598, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18165", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a redress scheme for victims of the Sodium Valproate scandal in line with recommendations in the Hughes Report.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747446", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747279, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18164", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it her policy that the proposed UKADS will assess the (a) environmental and (b) health impacts of new flight paths.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747346, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18163", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have made a (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful application for Pension Credit in each Parliamentary constituency since 1 April 2024; and how many people are awaiting a decision on their", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747346", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747409, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18162", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress his Department has made on extending the range of radio frequency directed energy weapons.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747409", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747408, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18161", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has had recent discussions with his international allies on the potential export of radio frequency directed energy weapons.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747408", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747407, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18160", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of procuring the radio frequency directed energy weapon capability.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747407", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747406, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18159", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 October 2024 to Question 3741 on Defence: Expenditure, how many additional documents have been included for consideration in Ministerial boxes as a result of changed thresholds for min", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747406", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747405, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18158", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department plans to spend on consultancy fees in (a) the 2024-25 financial year and (b) each remaining financial year of the Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747405", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747404, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18157", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has authorised any orders for Joint Air-to-Ground Missiles since the general election.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747404", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747403, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18156", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the capacity of the Army\u2019s fleet of heavy equipment transporters.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747403", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747401, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18155", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to oral answer of 13 November 2024 by the Minister of State, Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office, on Chagos Islands, Official Report, Column 793, what", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747401", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747397, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18154", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an estimate of the total number of heavy equipment transporters in service within the Army tabulated by those (a) currently available and (b) in maintenance.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747397", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747396, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18153", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November to Question 16232 on Global Combat Air Programme, whether his Department plans to separately ring-fence global combat air programme expenditure for (a) the core platform and ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747396", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747395, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18152", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his planned timetable is for publishing the next Equipment Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747395", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747393, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18151", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the RAF budget is for autonomous collaborative platforms in (a) 2024-25, (b) 2025-26, (c) 2026-27, (d) 2027-28, (e) 2028-2029 and (f) 2029-30 broken down by (i) R&D, (ii) procurement of platforms, (iii) supp", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747393", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747392, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18150", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 15458 on Military Aircraft: Helicopters, what capability gaps will exist in the interim period.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747392", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747389, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18149", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) requests for quotation and (b) requests for proposal were issued by his Department for new capabilities for the armed forces since July 2024 that were not (i) initiated by the previous Government and", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747389", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747387, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18148", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of (a) radio frequency directed energy weapons, (b) DragonFire lasers and (c) other directed energy weapons for the protection of (i) UK and (ii) United States Vis", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747387", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747385, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18147", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to undertake a full procurement of Radio Frequency Directed Energy Weapon capability.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747385", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747383, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18146", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to increase funding for R&D on Directed Energy Weapons.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747383", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747298, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18145", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will have discussions with Meta on the potential impact of (a) the adequacy of its customer support team and (b) accounts being temporarily disabled on UK businesses; and if he wi", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747328, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18144", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16506 on Israel Defence Forces, whether (a) UK-Israel military cooperation and (b) the sale of arms was discussed during the meeting between the Chief of the ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747328", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747386, "askingMemberId": 4399, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18143", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average award received through his Department's capital grant scheme was in (a) July, (b) August, (c) September, (d) October and (e) November.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747386", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747384, "askingMemberId": 4399, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18142", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many applications for the capital grant scheme were approved by his Department in each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747384", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747367, "askingMemberId": 4399, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18141", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many applications for the capital grant scheme were received by his Department in each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747367", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747365, "askingMemberId": 4399, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18140", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings she has had with the (a) National Farmers Union, (b) Country Land and Business Association, (c) Countryside Alliance, (d) Tenant Association Farmers and (e) Central Association for Agricultural Valuers", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747365", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747364, "askingMemberId": 4399, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18139", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings she had with the (a) National Farmers Union, (b) Country Land and Business Association, (c) Countryside Alliance, (d) Tenant Association Farmers and (e) Central Association for Agricultural Valuers bef", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747364", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747436, "askingMemberId": 4396, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18138", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of urgent provision of legal aid for leaseholders facing unfair charges.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747434, "askingMemberId": 4396, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18137", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the written statement by the Minister of State for Housing and Planning entitled Leasehold and Commonhold Reform of 21 November 2024, HCWS244, when the consulta", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747433, "askingMemberId": 4396, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18136", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the written statement by the Minister of State for Housing and Planning entitled Leasehold and Commonhold Reform of 21 November 2024, HCWS244, when the consulta", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747432, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18135", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many probation delivery units in England and Wales operate (a) a Linkworker Scheme and (b) another dedicated support scheme for people with acquired brain injury.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747431, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18134", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons in England and Wales operate (a) a Linkworker Scheme and (b) another dedicated support scheme for people with acquired brain injury.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747430, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18133", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what social care pathways are available for people whose acquired brain injury is identified when they are in the criminal justice system.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747429, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18132", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what health pathways are available for people whose acquired brain injury is identified when they are in the criminal justice system.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747428, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18131", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what percentage of service users of the commissioned probation services for neurodiverse needs have a (a) known and (b) suspected brain injury.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747427, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18130", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support the commissioned probation services for neurodiverse needs provides to people with an acquired brain injury.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747426, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18129", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance her Department has issued to probation professionals on the steps they should take if someone under post-custodial supervision is found to have previously had an acquired brain injury.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747425, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18128", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance her Department has issued to probation professionals on the steps they should take if someone with a community order is found to have previously had an acquired brain injury.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747424, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18127", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people aged (a) 14 to 17, (b) 18 to 25 and (c) 26 and older who were sentenced to community orders were screened for an acquired brain injury in the most recent period for which fi", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747424", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747423, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18126", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department issues on the steps the police should take when someone who enters police custody is found to have had an acquired brain injury.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747423", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747422, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18125", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of people aged (a) 14 to 17, (b) 18 to 25 and (c) 26 and older who were screened for acquired brain injury when they entered police custody were found to have a brain inju", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747422", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747421, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18124", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of people aged (a) 14 to 17, (b) 18 to 25 and (c) 26 and older who enter police custody were screened for acquired brain injury in the most recent period for which figures", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747421", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747511, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18123", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the BBC Eye Investigation televised on 2 December 2024, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Tesco, (b) Waitrose, (c) Asda and (b) Morrisons on product labelling.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747334, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18122", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help support humanitarian organisations in (a) Gaza and (b) Lebanon to prepare for winter.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747334", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747317, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18121", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information her Department holds on the number of cases in which location data for out-of-area placements made while discharging a homelessness duty is (a) not recorded or (", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747317", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747471, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18120", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has imposed (a) financial penalties and (b) adjustments to contract terms with General Dynamics in relation to the delay of the MORPHEUS project within the Land Environment Tactical Communi", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747468, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18119", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16468 on LE TacCIS programme, what the cost is of the Morpheus communications programme as of 5 December 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747468", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747466, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18118", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16468 on LE TacCIS programme, what the reasons are for the delay in the Morpheus communications project.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747466", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747463, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18117", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2024 to Question 16455 on Nuclear-free Zones: Treaties, whether talks between the UK and Mauritius covered the obligations of Mauritius under the Treaty of Pelindaba.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747463", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747460, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18116", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) mentors and (b) experts support projects backed through the Defence Innovation Accelerator for the North Atlantic European Regional Office; and at what cost.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747460", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747459, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18115", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on legacy UK obligations arising from the triggering by an EU country of Article 42(7) of the Treaty on European Union.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747459", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747458, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18114", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on engagement with the (a) EU Single Intelligence and Analysis Capacity, (b) projected EU Rapid Deployment Capacity and (c) planned EU Military Planning and Conduct Capability.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747458", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747457, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18113", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff at what grades are reviewing engagement with the EU through PESCO.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747457", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747456, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18112", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, Pursuant to the Answer of 8 October to Question 5333 on Defence: Procurement, what other projects which align with UK interests his Department is exploring on a project-by-project basis.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747456", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747455, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18111", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department is holding discussions with (a) European and (b) EU counterparts on changes to binding PESCO commitments.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747455", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747454, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18110", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, Pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2024 to Question 7499 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty, whether the agreement covers the employment of descendants of Chagos islanders on the base on Diego Garci", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747454", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747453, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18109", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, Pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2024 to Question 7499 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty, whether the agreement covers the employment of third country nationals on the base on Diego Garcia.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747450, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18108", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, Pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2024 to Question 7499 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty, whether he Mauritian government may permit foreign direct investment into the Chagos islands.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747448, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18107", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2024 to Question 7499 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty, what right of access to BIOT territorial waters will be permitted to third parties.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747444, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18106", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2024 to Question 7499 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty, whether the Mauritian government will have the right to allow (a) basing on, (b) occupancy of and (c) acc", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747443, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18105", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, Pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2024 to Question 7499 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty, what right of (a) access, (b) inspection and (c) veto the Mauritian Government will have to the Chagos ba", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747440, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18104", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2024 to Question 7499 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty, whether (a) assets and (b) staff of the Mauritian armed forces will be (i) proximately and (ii) co- locat", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747303, "askingMemberId": 185, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "18103", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will take steps to ensure that the Insolvency Service investigates landlords that do not follow tribunal rent rulings to pay back monies owed.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747303", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747302, "askingMemberId": 185, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18102", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will take steps to ensure that landlords who are found liable for rent repayment orders in tribunal pay back monies owed.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747302", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747391, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18101", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will visit the Griffin Institute at Northwick Park Hospital in Brent West constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747391", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747390, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-16T00:00:00", "uin": "18100", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a national training centre for robotic surgery within the NHS to provide surgical training that is independent of the manufactu", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747390", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747388, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-16T00:00:00", "uin": "18099", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to use (a) robots and (b) AI to help support training on innovative surgical techniques.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747388", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747370, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-16T00:00:00", "uin": "18098", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information her Department holds on when the Building Safety Regulator plans to respond to the applications for (a) Gateway 2 and (b) Gateway 3 approval for the two high ris", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747363, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-16T00:00:00", "uin": "18097", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to tackle delays in approvals for Gateway (a) 2 and (b) 3 submissions to the Building Safety Regulator.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747363", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746478, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17541", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of UK sanctions on Chinese (a) people and (b) businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746891, "askingMemberId": 1508, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18096", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 July 2024 to Question 1488 on Agriculture: Food Supply, if he will have discussions with the Prime Minister on holding a farm to fork summit at 10 Downing ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746891", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747013, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18095", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to increase the level of financial support for low-income families with more than two children.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747013", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747012, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18094", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to help tackle child poverty.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747012", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747011, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18093", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that children from low-income families have the same level of access to (a) high-quality education and (b) a range of options for schools as those from higher-incom", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747011", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746962, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18092", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the support services available to victims of modern slavery; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure these services are (a) accessible and (b)", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746962", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746961, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18091", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of its policies on tackling modern slavery.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746961", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746960, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18090", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her international counterparts on tackling (a) human trafficking and (b) modern slavery across borders.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746960", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746959, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18089", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure law enforcement agencies are equipped with the necessary (a) training and (b) resources to (i) identify and (ii) tackle modern slavery cases effectively.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746959", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746958, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18088", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to stop modern slavery practices within supply chains (a) domestically and (b) internationally.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746958", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746930, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18087", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of existing waste incineration facilities for the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746930", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746929, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18086", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will widen the eligibility of free school meals to all children whose parents are in receipt of Universal Credit.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746929", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746928, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18085", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to increase funding for (a) universal infant free school meals and (b) benefitted free school meals.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746928", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747109, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18084", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of additional Government-funded Adult Education Centres across Cornwall.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747103, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18083", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support adult education in Cornwall.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747055, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18082", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of a system for dispute resolution available to freeholders paying estate management fees.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747055", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747166, "askingMemberId": 5348, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18081", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase uptake among schools for Universal SEND Services in Hertfordshire.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747164, "askingMemberId": 5348, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18080", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of mandated Continuing Professional Development activities for increasing Special Educational Needs and Disability services in Hertfordshire.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747137, "askingMemberId": 5344, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18079", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will publish a list of embassies ranked by the number of times they have met Organisations of Persons with Disabilities in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747135, "askingMemberId": 5344, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18078", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, which UK ambassadors have met Organisations of Persons with Disabilities in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747132, "askingMemberId": 5344, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18077", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many and what proportion of UK Ambassadors have met with Organisations of Persons with Disabilities in the past year.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747196, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18076", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the (a) mental health and (b) social needs of kidney patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747195, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve (a) urology and (b) continence services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747194, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help encourage more people to become organ donors.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747192, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle health inequality caused by childhood poverty.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747191, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18072", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help support (a) pre-school, (b) primary school and (c) secondary school-aged children living in poverty other than through the provision of free school meals.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747190, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his department is taking to help protect chalk streams from (a) pollution and (b) overextraction.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747184, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18070", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel were referred to mental health services in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747182, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many incidents of (a) mould, (b) fire, and (c) flooding were recorded in military service personnel housing in each month in (a) 2022 and (b) 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747180, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of his Department\u2019s firearms were (a) lost and (b) stolen in each month in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746946, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18067", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the FTE staff hours that have been saved (a) in total and (b) per practice as a result of GPs using online forms promoted in the \u2018Help Us Help You\u2019 advertising scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746946", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746945, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the potential cost saving to the public purse of GP's using online appointment forms promoted in the Help Us to Help You advertising scheme (a) in total and", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746945", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746944, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18065", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of GP practices use online forms promoted in the Help us Help You advertising scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746944", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746989, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18064", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to support those with criminal records to reintegrate back into appropriate work.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746989", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746907, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employee settlement agreements there were in her Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746907", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746906, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18062", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many employee settlement agreements there were in her Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746906", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746905, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18061", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many employee settlement agreements there were in his Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746905", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746904, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18060", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employee settlement agreements there were in her Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746904", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746903, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18059", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employee settlement agreements there were in her Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746903", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746902, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18058", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many employee settlement agreements there were in his Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746902", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746901, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18057", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many employee settlement agreements there were in his Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746901", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746900, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18056", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employee settlement agreements there were in her Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746900", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746899, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18055", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many employee settlement agreements there were in her Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746899", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746898, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18054", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many employee settlement agreements there were in his Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746898", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746897, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18053", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many employee settlement agreements there were in his Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746897", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746896, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18052", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many employee settlement agreements there were in his Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746896", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746895, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18051", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many employee settlement agreements there were in her Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746895", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746894, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18050", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many employee settlement agreements there were in his Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746894", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746893, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18049", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many employee settlement agreements there were in his Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746893", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746892, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18048", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, how many employee settlement agreements there were in her Department in each year since 2020; and what the total value of such agreements is.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746892", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746979, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18047", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to (a) assess and (b) prevent unauthorised sub-letting of social housing for holiday lets.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746979", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747108, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18046", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that (a) the most\u00a0vulnerable and (b) other people living in rural constituencies can easily access her Department's support (i) digitally and (ii) through local office", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747020, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18045", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when her Department plans to make a decision on the planning application for a solar facility at the University of Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747020", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746943, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18044", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing measures to prevent households that have chosen not to install smart meters from higher energy tariffs.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746943", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746942, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18043", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing separate inheritance tax thresholds for (a) agricultural land and (b) business equipment for farmers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746942", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746941, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18042", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing measures to reduce the hope value of land.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746941", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746940, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18041", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing funding to ensure that the Lifelong Links programme can be extended to all children in care.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746940", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746937, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18040", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what her Department's timescales are for bringing forward secondary legislation in relation to the Leasehold Act 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746937", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747088, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18039", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will prioritise global health spending in the Overseas Development Assistance budget in (a) 2024-25 and (b) 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747088", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747087, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18038", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make it his policy to support (a) low and (b) middle income countries issuing compulsory licenses for the HIV prevention tool lenacapavir.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747087", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747086, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18037", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to increase the amount of health-related content in the national curriculum.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747086", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747084, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18036", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to monitor the rise in cases in the more spreadable variant of mpox now detected in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747082, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18035", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, by what procedure central government funding is allocated to institutions providing hospice care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747054, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18034", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost of the increase to employers National Insurance contributions for Suffolk Constabulary in the 2025-26 financial year; and how much additional funding her Departm", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747054", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747053, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18033", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what grounds she decided the level of funding for Suffolk Constabulary; and if she will review that funding.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747053", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747048, "askingMemberId": 5298, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18032", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of General Practitioners in rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747048", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747124, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18031", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the Glis Glis (edible dormouse) on (a) indigenous species and (b) property; and whether he plans to take steps to reduce this i", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747110, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "18030", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the New Hospital Programme review, when the (a) options and (b) recommendations for the Royal Berkshire Hospital, Reading will be published; and when he plans to announce which ho", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746950, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18029", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to publish the independent review of her Department\u2019s language services.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746950", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746949, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18028", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to ensure the adequacy of services provided by interpreters to her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746949", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746948, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18027", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of replacing external (a) translation and (b) interpretation services provided to her Department with services provided by departmental staff.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746948", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747114, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18026", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether ETSU-R-97 is (a) the only framework methodology used for the assessment of onshore wind turbines and (b) the most (i) effective and (ii) up to date guidance; what assessm", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747072, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18025", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current level of spending on heavy rail infrastructure in Wales is.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747072", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747129, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18024", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will update the Decent Homes Standard to include floor coverings in social rented properties.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747127, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18023", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will issue guidance to registered social housing providers which confirms that if a floor covering exists in a property when the tenancy changes over that the default will", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747016, "askingMemberId": 5272, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18022", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to ensure (a) landlords and (b) management companies are held accountable for safety defects in leasehold properties.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747016", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747091, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18021", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve support for families affected by baby loss including (a) access to counselling services, (b) support for siblings and (c) training for healthcare prof", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747091", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747107, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18020", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to (a) recognise domestic abuse as a form of violence against women and girls, (b) prioritise funding for specialist services, (c) implement reforms to family court", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746969, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18019", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on funding for public sector pay awards in Northern Ireland; and whether she has allocated funding to ensure parity in pay offers for public sector wo", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746969", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747081, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18018", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle the theft of mobile phones.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747080, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18017", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to reform pay policies at the National Crime Agency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747079, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18016", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of rules on local connection for housing allocations.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747078, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18015", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to remove the requirement for a local connection for (a) homeless veterans, (b) survivors of domestic abuse and (c) care leavers.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747099, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18014", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 on Question 16304, how many pensioner households who are in receipt of Housing Benefit and who have been identified as being potentially entitled to, but not cl", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747023, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18013", "questionText": "To ask the Leader of the House, when she plans to update the Cabinet Office Guide to Making Legislation to provide guidance on the environmental principles duty in section 19(1) of the Environment Act 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 34, "answeringBodyName": "Leader of the House", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747023", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747019, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18012", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether (a) templates and (b) guidance for (i) ministerial submissions, (ii) the write round process, (iii) post implementation reviews of legislation and (iv) the preparation of departmental business cases have", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747019", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747018, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18011", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he plans to update guidance for the Better Regulation Framework to include section 19(1) of the Environment Act 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747018", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747015, "askingMemberId": 5241, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18010", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what his Department's planned timetable is for concluding negotiations on the UK-Armenia Comprehensive and Enhanced Partnership Agreement; and what steps he is taking to supp", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747015", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747160, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18009", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the timeframe for PIP award reviews; whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of waiting times for appeal on PIP applicants; and what st", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746926, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18008", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department plans to respond to the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme Review 2020, published on 16 July 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746926", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747038, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18007", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2024 to Question 15983 on General Practitioners: Kent, how much it cost to set up Bromleag Care Practice in 2019.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747017, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18006", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 15980 on Gatwick Airport, whether the previous Secretary of State for Transport met with groups opposing Gatwick Airport expansion.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747017", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746916, "askingMemberId": 5217, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18005", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Residual Waste Infrastructure Capacity Note will make an assessment of the adequacy of (a) incineration capacity and (b) potential feedstock availability in the light of (i", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746916", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747104, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18004", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what place food manufacturing will have in the industrial strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747050, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "18003", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his trade strategy will support the aims of the Fairtrade movement.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747050", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746931, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18002", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Education in response to the question from the hon. Member for Wokingham of Tuesday 3 December, Official Report, column 96WH, if she will wri", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746931", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746977, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18001", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the public bodies for which his Department is responsible.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746977", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746976, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "18000", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the (a) materials and (b) critical minerals sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746976", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746975, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17999", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the steel sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746975", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746974, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17998", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the (a) maritime and (b) shipbuilding sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746974", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746973, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17997", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the construction sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746973", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746939, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17996", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what his Department's timetable is for lowering energy bills for people in Bromsgrove constituency, in the context of the Great British Energy Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746939", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746936, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17995", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many additional police officers her Department plans to fund in West Mercia by the end of 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746936", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746918, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17994", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she made of the potential impact of increases in employer National Insurance contributions on charities prior the the announcement of the Autumn Budget 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746918", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747145, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17993", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has had discussions with her Australian counterpart on the impact of excise tax for tobacco products on (a) consumer and (b) organised crime group behaviour.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747142, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17992", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the potential increase in illegal tobacco sales as a consequence of the implementation of a generational ban on tobacco sales.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747140, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17991", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government will take steps to support the mental health of shopkeepers responsible with enforcing the implementation of a generational ban on tobacco sales.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747138, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17990", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the potential increase in incidents of (a) violent crime, (b) physical abuse and (c) verbal intimidation against shopkeepers as a result of a generational ban on toba", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747218, "askingMemberId": 5160, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17989", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to review the current Shoreline Management Plans.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747070, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17988", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are on the terror watchlist broken down by ideological motivation.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747070", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747068, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17987", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants receive private healthcare through work schemes by Department.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747068", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747058, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17986", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the benefits of a review of the cost effectiveness of the care home vaccine mandate during COVID.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747058", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747056, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17985", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the cost effectiveness of the covid-19 vaccine booster programme, in the context of the findings on the impact of vaccination take-up in care homes on resident mort", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747056", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747046, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17984", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many deportations have not taken place due to mental health concerns in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747046", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747041, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17983", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many trials have not taken place as a result of the defendant being deemed not fit for trial due to mental health conditions in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747036, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17982", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an estimate of the number of children who are (a) irregular migrants and (b) were on school rolls on 4 December 2024 broken down by age.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747036", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747034, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17981", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of irregular migrants arriving by small boat possessed (a) a passport and (b) another form of identification in each year since 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747034", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747033, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17980", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied asylum-seeking children under 18 absconded and did not return last year.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747033", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747027, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17979", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on refugees visiting their country of origin whilst still resident in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747027", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747025, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17978", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16274 on Undocumented Migrants: Age Assurance, what the nature is of the further comprehensive age assessment.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747025", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747024, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17977", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16274 on Undocumented Migrants: Age Assurance, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of using bone density testing for all undocu", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747024", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746915, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17976", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the number of irregular migrants processed at Western Jet Foil did not match the number processed at Manston Immigration Centre since February 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746915", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746914, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17975", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents involving improvised weapons have been recorded at Manston Immigration Centre since February 2022; and what weapons were used in those incidents.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746914", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746913, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17974", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many female migrants have reported sexual assault in Manston Immigration Centre in each of the last ten years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746913", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746912, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17973", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department developed plans to use roll-on/roll-off ferries to bring irregular migrants to the UK from France in 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746912", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746911, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17972", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of her Department's policy not to initiate fraud investigations under \u00a35,000 on public finances.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746911", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746909, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17971", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, to provide a breakdown of all religious festivals celebrated by the Department in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746909", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747216, "askingMemberId": 5155, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17970", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS prescriptions for cannabis based products there have been in each year since 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747214, "askingMemberId": 5155, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17969", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has has been made on ensuring appropriate treatment for people suffering from epilepsy; and what steps he has taken to implement the 2018 review by Dame Sally Davies on the therape", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747213, "askingMemberId": 5155, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17968", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what community-led rural gigabit broadband projects are in development with Building Digital UK.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747212, "askingMemberId": 5155, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17967", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to support rural community organisations undertaking community-led broadband installations.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747211, "askingMemberId": 5155, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17966", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) support research into and (b) promote awareness of (i) Guillain-Barr\u00e9 Syndrome, (ii) Chronic Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy and (iii) other related inflamm", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747205, "askingMemberId": 5155, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17965", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the Spirit Drinks Verification Scheme on small-scale craft production.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747203, "askingMemberId": 5155, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17964", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking taken to (a) encourage growth in, (b) support small scale craft produce in and (c) reduce barriers to entry to the spirits industry.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747198, "askingMemberId": 5155, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17963", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has had recent discussion with the Scottish government on the Cladding Remediation Programme in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747197, "askingMemberId": 5155, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17962", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent progress she has been made in removing dangerous cladding from building across the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746957, "askingMemberId": 5151, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17961", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to reduce dropout rates of students studying\u00a0T-Levels.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746957", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746954, "askingMemberId": 5151, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17960", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve (a) recruitment and (b) retention in the further education sector.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746954", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746953, "askingMemberId": 5151, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17959", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle land banking.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746953", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747002, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17958", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to implement a national food strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747002", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747000, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17957", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to ensure that at least 50% of all food purchased by the public sector is (a) locally produced and (b) sustainable.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747000", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746999, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17956", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will conduct a review of the funding model for school meals in (a) locally maintained and (b) Multi Academy Trust schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746999", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746998, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17955", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to announce the rates that will be paid to (a) locally maintained and (b) Multi Academy Trust schools for universal infant free school meals this academic year.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746998", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746997, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17954", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to take further steps to ensure that Government Food Standards are adhered to in (a) locally maintained and (b) Multi Academy Trust schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746997", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746996, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17953", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the guidance entitled School food standards: resources for schools, published on 26 March 2019, what recent steps her Department has taken to ensure that this guidance is being followed in all", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746996", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747179, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17952", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether his Department uses journalistic reporting from Palestinian journalists in Gaza when conducting assessments into (a) the humanitarian situation and (b) Israeli milita", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747178, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17951", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the Committee to Protect Journalists press release entitled, Journalist casualties in the Israel", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747177, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17950", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to help protect (a) journalists and (b) media workers (i) based and (ii) operating in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747176, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17949", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his planned timetable is for when cancer sites will have recurrence data collection mandated to align with the collection of breast cancer recurrence data.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747175, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17948", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take ensure there is sufficient provision of (a) rehabilitation and (b) prehabilitation for cancer patients across all cancer alliances.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747173, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17947", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to help improve (a) access to GP appointments and (b) rates of early-stage cancer diagnosis in areas of socio-economic deprivation in Yorkshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747172, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17946", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will have discussions with social care providers on the potential impact of Autumn Budget 2024 on the social care sector.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747171, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17945", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to provide additional funding to local authorities to meet the increased costs of social care.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746955, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17944", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to help ensure that legitimate knife manufacturers are not adversely affected by online restrictions intended to reduce knife crime.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746955", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747120, "askingMemberId": 5133, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17943", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the provision of community accessible covered tennis courts in underserved communities.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747057, "askingMemberId": 5133, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17942", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when his Department last raised the rights of women and girls in Afghanistan in the (a) UN Human Rights Council and (b) General Assembly.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747057", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747026, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-12T00:00:00", "uin": "17940", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make it her policy to reduce the VAT (a) rate and (b) threshold for businesses that provide personal care services.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747026", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747105, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17939", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will ensure the Post Office withdraws the five-year Transformation Plan published on 13 November 2024..", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746883, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17938", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to expedite compensation for nuclear test veterans.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746883", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747040, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17937", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government\u2019s independent adviser on political violence and disruption has had meetings with representatives of (a) Leonardo, (b) Glencore, (c) Enwell Energy, (d) BP and (e) Centrica since ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747037, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17936", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer on 2 December 2024 to Question 15939 on Electric Vehicles: Charging Points, whether she is taking steps to analyse pricing data to compare the cost of using (a) public and (b) home electr", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747037", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746978, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17935", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will publish an evaluation of the pilot scheme on the use of single-named caseworkers by the Child Maintenance Service.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746978", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746966, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17934", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Establishing the Infected Blood Compensation Scheme in Regulations, published on 23 August 2024, what his planned timetable is to publish the second set ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746966", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747217, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17933", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16252 on Flood Control: Cambridgeshire, what steps the Government is taking to improve the condition of the Environment Agency's h", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747168, "askingMemberId": 5083, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17932", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the potential for the Child Maintenance System to be used as a tool of economic abuse.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747167, "askingMemberId": 5083, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17931", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to publish the feedback from the consultation on the Child Maintenance System.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747165, "askingMemberId": 5083, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17930", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people with diagnosed HIV who are not currently in care; what research it has conducted into the reasons for disengagement from care; and what", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747163, "askingMemberId": 5083, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17929", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to extend opt-out HIV testing beyond emergency departments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747162, "askingMemberId": 5083, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17928", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to continue funding for the opt-out blood-borne virus testing programme at (a) St George's, Epsom and (b) St Helier Hospitals and Health Group beyond March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747161, "askingMemberId": 5083, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17927", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department are taking to tackle changes in rates of HIV diagnoses among heterosexual men and women.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747159, "askingMemberId": 5083, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17926", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of facilities staff are on Agenda For Change contracts.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747158, "askingMemberId": 5083, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17925", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of shortages of building inspectors on (a) repairs and (b) maintenance projects across the NHS Estate.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747157, "askingMemberId": 5083, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17924", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the prior consultation on the Down Syndrome Act 2022; and when he plans to publish the statutory guidance.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747130, "askingMemberId": 5083, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17923", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of Climate Change education in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747045, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17922", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has made an estimate of the number of SEND pupils in (a) Leicester East constituency and (b) England impacted by changes to the bus fare cap.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747043, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17921", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support young SEND people not in education, employment or training.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747042, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17920", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent diplomatic steps he has taken to help ensure the protection of (a) Hindu communities and (b) other religious minorities in Bangladesh.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747010, "askingMemberId": 5067, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "17919", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) commencing the move-on period for newly-recognised refugees only after access to their e-visa has been confirmed and (b) extending the mov", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747010", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747032, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17918", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2024 to Question 12545 on Asylum: Sri Lanka, whether her Department sought information from the Sri Lankan government on the criminal records of Sri Lankan nation", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747031, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17917", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2024 to Question 12545 on Asylum: Sri Lanka, what the serious welfare and safeguarding concerns for (a) children and (b) other people were on Diego Garcia.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747031", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747030, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17916", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has provided information to UK police forces on the Sri Lankan asylum seekers in Diego Garcia transferred to the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747029, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17915", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any of the Sri Lankan asylum seekers on Diego Garcia have been excluded from travel to the UK on the grounds of (a) their criminal convictions and (b) ongoing criminal investigations.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747029", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747028, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17914", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the Sri Lankan asylum seekers on Diego Garcia have been transferred to the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747028", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746935, "askingMemberId": 5044, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17913", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing an Online Safety Act fee regime through which the fees charged to individual platforms is equal to the costs to Ofc", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746935", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746934, "askingMemberId": 5044, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17912", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, with reference to the consultation document entitled Online Safety - fees and penalties: Consultation on implementing fees and penalties under the Online Safety Act 2023, published on 2", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746934", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746933, "askingMemberId": 5044, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17911", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, with reference to the consultation document entitled Online Safety - fees and penalties: Consultation on implementing fees and penalties under the Online Safety Act 2023, published on 2", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746933", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746910, "askingMemberId": 4938, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17910", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to provide additional interim healthcare services to people affected by the relocation of the North Birmingham Urgent Treatment Centre to Good Hope Hospital.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746910", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747189, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17909", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) end and (b) prevent strike action by hospital facilities staff.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747187, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17908", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the potential impact of hospital facilities staff strikes on patient wellbeing.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747144, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17907", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many computer monitors his Department has provided to (a) Ministers and (b) officials for home working since 5 July 2024; and what the cost to public purse was.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747126, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17906", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, when he plans to respond to the letter of 28 November 2024 from the hon. Member for Arundel and South Downs.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747125, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17905", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the hospitality sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747123, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17904", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what information his Department holds on G20 states that have set a target to end the sale of new (a) solely internal combustion engine powered vehicles and (b) hybrid vehicles powered in part by inter", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747122, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17903", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the Minister of State for Trade Policy and Economic Security's oral contribution of 3 December 2024, Official Report, column 174, whether his Department has conducted any independent ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746889, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17902", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it remains Government policy to provide \u00a3978 million funding for transport projects in Tees Valley.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746889", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747051, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17901", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of vision rehabilitation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747051", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746885, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17900", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has she made on the adequacy of of passenger facilities at Crewe railway station as a connection point for service between the North West and (a) the West Midlands and (b) the South East.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746885", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746884, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17899", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has she made on the number of points failures on the rail network in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746884", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747174, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17898", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure consistency of the supply of medication for (a) epilepsy and b) Parkinson's disease patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747065, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17897", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to the public purse of nationalising Greater Anglia.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747065", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747061, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17896", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to the public purse of nationalising C2C.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747061", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747060, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17895", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the cost of nationalising South Western Railway.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747060", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747202, "askingMemberId": 4780, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17894", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact on schools of ending the academy conversion support grant.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747201, "askingMemberId": 4780, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17893", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact on schools of ending the academy conversion support grant.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747200, "askingMemberId": 4780, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17892", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils with SEND who currently attend independent schools do not have an Education, Health and Care plan.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747199, "askingMemberId": 4780, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17891", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 5.20 of the Spring Budget 2024, published on 6 March 2024, HC 560, what her policy is on building 15 new special free schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747083, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17890", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish hid Department's final delivery plan on Myalgic encephalomyelitis (M.E.).", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747170, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17889", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to issue statutory guidance on the provision of absorbent products for adult incontinence products.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747169, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17888", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure the weekly personal expense allowance for those living in care homes is increased by the rate of inflation each financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747119, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17887", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has met the nuclear test veteran campaign group.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747118, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17886", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what the evidential basis is for the levels of Extended Producer Responsibility fee for (a) steel food cans, (b) fibre-based cartons and (c) plastic pouches.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747117, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17885", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to help protect leaseholders from (a) excessive ground rents and (b) other exploitative practices in the period until secondary legislation is implemente", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747116, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17884", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when she plans to implement secondary legislation under the Leasehold and Freehold Reform Act 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747115, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17883", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to tackle funding gaps between (a) mental and (b) physical health services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747113, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17882", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) reimbursement schemes and (b) financial assistance programmes for patients seeking private dental care because of NHS delays.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747111, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17881", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that residents of Ashfield constituency are able to access essential postal services.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747154, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17880", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve access to further education facilities for young people in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747152, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17879", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what recent steps he has taken to help improve broadband connectivity in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747151, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17878", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to help increase the availability of detached youth work in rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746925, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17877", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2024 to Question 15704 on Jobcentres and Universal Credit: Telephone Services, how many calls were translated by language code since 2021; and what the cost was of t", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746925", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747059, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17876", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to reduce the cost of motor insurance premiums for young drivers in (a) Runcorn postcodes and (b) England.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747059", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747052, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17875", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to end homelessness in the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747052", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747049, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17874", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to increase the net supply of social housing in the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747049", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747047, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17873", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of an annual state pension increase for British pensioners living outside the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747047", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747039, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17872", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to increase investment in high streets in (a) the North West and (b) Runcorn and Helsby constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747035, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17871", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of the changes to employers National Insurance contributions on the financial situation of hospices.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747035", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747005, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17870", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make assessment of the adequacy of diagnosis times for bowel cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747005", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747004, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17869", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of giving health and care workers on Tier 2 visas a certificate of common sponsorship.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747004", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746964, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17868", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of creating a tracking coding system to record people in temporary accommodation that access health services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746964", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746963, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17867", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of offering free bus travel for homeless (a) children and (b) adults living in temporary accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746963", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747102, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17866", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure translators used by police forces are impartial.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747101, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17865", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a (a) hotline for reporting and (b) focus group on (i) politically motivated assaults and (ii) transnational repression.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747076, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17864", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure sponsor licenses are processed within the service standards timeframes.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747076", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746917, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17863", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure (a) consistency of care and (b) availability of medication for people with an ADHD diagnosis who move to a different NHS Trust from the one in which th", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746917", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746908, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17862", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children living in relative poverty are not eligible for free school meals.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746908", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746971, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17861", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Afghan counterpart on the treatment of women and girls in that country.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746971", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746967, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17860", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the Taliban's decision to (a) ban women from medical training and (b) prohibit male medics from ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746967", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747153, "askingMemberId": 4616, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17859", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the KPMG interim investigation of December 2022 into Drax Power Station\u2019s claims for government subsidy.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747009, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17858", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number and proportion of 999 calls that were made in Scotland and handled by an Ambulance Service in England and Wales since 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747009", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747146, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17857", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what case studies she has used to calculate the financial impact of proposed changes to Agricultural Property Relief.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747143, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17856", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the changes to inheritance tax on the financial viability of small family farms in (a) Kent and (b) Faversham and Mid Kent cons", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747141, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17855", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the economic contribution of farming to (a) Kent and (b) Faversham and Mid Kent constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747139, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17854", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an estimate of the number of farmers who will exit the sector as a result of the change to agricultural property relief in the Autumn Budget.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747136, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17853", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many farms were subject to inheritance tax in Faversham and Mid Kent constituency in the (a) 2019-20, (b) 2020-21 and (c) 2021-22 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747134, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17852", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of changes to (a) agricultural and (b) business property relief in the Autumn Budget on family-owned farms in (a) Kent and (b) Faversham and Mid Kent constituency", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747133, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17851", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking with the Secretary of State for the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs to help ensure the generational continuity of agricultural businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747131, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17850", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance she plans to issue to small business farmers who wish to keep an inherited family farm.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747128, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17849", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of changes to agricultural property relief in the Autumn Budget 2024 on the sustainability of domestic food production.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747100, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17848", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has instituted a freeze in his Department on new procurement to satisfy Urgent Capability Requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747098, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17847", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when Ministers from his Department have met representatives of the Maldives Government to discuss the future of the Chagos Islands since 4 July 2024; and which Minister met which representative of the Maldives on", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747097, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17846", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when Ministers from his Department have met representatives of the Chagossian community since 4 July 2024; and which Minister met how many Chagossians on each such occasion.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747096, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17845", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when Ministers from his Department have met representatives of the Maldives Government to discuss the future of the Chagos Islands since 4 July 2024; and which Minister met w", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747095, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17844", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when Ministers from his Department have met representatives of the Chagossian community since 4 July 2024; and which Minister met how many Chagossians on each such occasion.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747092, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17843", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the oral Answer by the Minister for the Armed Forces on 2 December 2024, Official Report, Column 27, if he will make an estimate of the cost to his Departme", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747069, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17842", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 17024 on Defence Equipment and Support, whether he has instructed his Department to put a hold on new procurement in this financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747069", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747067, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17841", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost has been of (a) capital and (b) non-capital expenditure on (i) HMS Albion, (ii) HMS Bulwark, (iii) HMS Northumberland, (iv) RFA Wave Knight and (v) RFA Wave Ruler in each of the last five financial ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747067", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747066, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17840", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral Answer by the Minister for the Armed Forces on 2 December 2024, Official Report, Column 27, what the estimated cost to the US will be of the Chagos settlement excluding the Government-t", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747066", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747063, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17839", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral Answer by the Minister for the Armed Forces on 2 December 2024, Official Report, Column 27, if he will make an estimate of the cost to his Department of implementing the proposed UK-Mau", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747063", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747062, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17838", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his oral Answer to the hon. Member for South Suffolk of 11 November 2024, Official Report, Column 505, whether he plans to provide information on the cost of (a) direct payments made to the gove", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747062", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747193, "askingMemberId": 4511, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "17837", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase provision for NHS dentists in Ealing Central and Acton constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746965, "askingMemberId": 4493, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17836", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle poverty for people on low incomes; and if she will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a statutory duty to progressively reduce levels of ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746965", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747003, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17835", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the planned merger of Local Government Pension Scheme funds will require legislation; and on what (a) geography or (b) criteria the new merged funds will be based.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747003", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747001, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17834", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions she has visited the QEII Centre since the general election; and if she will visit the GB News studio in the centre.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747001", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746995, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17833", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans the Local Government and Social Care Ombudsman has to issue guidance on issuing of litter fines to householders.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746995", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746994, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17832", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Report on the 2024 UK Parliamentary general election and the May 2024 elections, published by the Electoral Commission in November 2024. what plans she has ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746994", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746993, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17831", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the recommendations on electoral (a) law and (b) administration in the Report on the 2024 UK Parlia", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746993", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746992, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17830", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department's consultation entitled Modern leasehold: restricting ground rent for existing leases, updated on 8 December 2023, when she plans to respond to t", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746992", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746991, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17829", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 15 November 2024, to Question 12952, on Devolution: Suffolk, whether combined county authorities should contain (a) one county council or (b) more than ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746991", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746990, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17828", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2024 to Question 10991, on Civil Service: Zero Hours Contracts, how many departmental (a) staff and (b) contractors are on zero hour contrac", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746990", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746984, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17827", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the increased revenue to the public purse generated by the increase in business rates for private schools from 2025-26 onwards will be (a) kept in full by local government, (b) shared between central and loc", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746984", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746982, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17826", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information her Department holds on the average ranking for local authorities in (a) urban, (b) suburban and (c) rural areas on the Index of Multiple Deprivation in the late", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746982", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746980, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17825", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2024 to Question 13412 on Local Government Finance, whether she plans to reduce funding for councils not in areas of high deprivation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746980", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746888, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17824", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to freeze the small business rate relief multiplier while adjusting for the revaluation in 2026-27.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746888", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747121, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17823", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential importance of business support functionalities by online platforms such as META.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747112, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17822", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to protect the accounts of online businesses business from being erroneously temporarily disabled.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747022, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17821", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 15757 on Agricultural Products: UK Trade with EU, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential financial impact ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747022", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746921, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17820", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to oral contribution of 3 December 2024 by the Chief Secretary to the Treasury, if she will make an overall estimate of the impact of the UK\u2019s exit from the EU.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746921", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746920, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17819", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of proposed changes to Home Office English Language Testing services on the British Council\u2019s (a) finances and (b) abili", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746920", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746919, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17818", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to help ensure that the British Council has adequate funding to effectively promote (a) Scottish and (b) wider UK (i) education and (ii) arts.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746919", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747044, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17817", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral contribution of the then Minister of State in her Department during the Ninth sitting of the Public Bill Committee on the Victims and Prisoners Bill on 4 July 2023, Official Report colu", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746922, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17816", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with refence to the oral contribution of 6 November 2024 by the Minister for Trade Policy and Economic Security, Official Report column 70WH, how the solar stewardship initiative will support", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746922", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747094, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17815", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of including renewable liquid gases in the green taxonomy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747021, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17814", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on how many registered farmers there are in each constituency in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747021", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746887, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17813", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of increasing the payments made to women for their eggs from 1 October 2024 on trends in the number of (a) low income women and (b) students wh", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746887", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747215, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17812", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16156 on Turing Scheme: Free School Meals, how many and what proportion of students with Turing grants are from disadvantaged backgrounds.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747210, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17811", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2024 to Question 16157 on Railways: Nationalisation, whether her Department plans to maintain regional livery as railway franchises are brought into public ownership.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747209, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17810", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to help improve the accessibility of information at bus stops for disabled people.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747208, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17809", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to help improve the provision of real time information at bus stops.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747207, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17808", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what training civil servants in his Department receive on the public sector equality duty.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747206, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17807", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what the budget is for the Government Office for Technology Transfer in the 2025-26 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747204, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17806", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, with reference to the Government\u2019s response to the Independent Review of the UK\u2019s Research, Development and Innovation Organisational Landscape, what steps he has taken to explore a sus", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747156, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17805", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, which Minister is responsible for the interface between innovation and business to drive growth.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747155, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17804", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, with reference to the Strategic Partnership Arrangement 2024 between Microsoft and the Crown Commercial Service, what guidance is available to civil servants on the use of Microsoft Co-", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747150, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17803", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, with reference to the Strategic Partnership Arrangement 2024 between Microsoft and the Crown Commercial Service, what guidance is available to civil servants on securing official docume", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747149, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17802", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2024 to Question 12938 on Research Finance, what proportion of the \u00a3500m allocated to his Department for spend on research and developmen", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747148, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17801", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2024 to Question 11881 on Research Finance, what proportion of the \u00a3335m allocated to his Department for spend on research and developmen", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747188, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17800", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the professional services sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747186, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17799", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the retail sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747185, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17798", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the infrastructure sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747183, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17797", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the consumer goods sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747181, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17796", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the defence and security manufacturing sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746886, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17795", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, which companies have applied to operate a small modular reactor.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746886", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746972, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "17794", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has had discussions with the Financial Conduct Authority on regulation of digital assets.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746972", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746968, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "17793", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to promote the UK as a place for international investment in digital assets.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746968", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747008, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17792", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Written Statement of 4 December 2024, HCWS281 on Railway Passenger Services, whether she plans to (a) improve (i) step-free access and (ii) rail infrastructure for Greater Anglia services ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747008", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747007, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17791", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Written Statement of 4 December 2024, HCWS281 on Railway Passenger Services, what plans she has to review (a) service quality, (b) ticket pricing, (c) the business model and (d) timetables", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747007", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747006, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17790", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Written Statement of 4 December 2024, HCWS281 on Railway Passenger Services, what plans she has to consult (a) Members of Parliament, (b) local authorities, (c) passenger representatives a", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747006", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747093, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17789", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of forthcoming changes to business rate relief on the viability of grassroots music venues.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747014, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17788", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to review the Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities Involving Animals) (England) Regulations 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747014", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747071, "askingMemberId": 4020, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17787", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he plans to continue investment in national space data activities.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747071", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747147, "askingMemberId": 4018, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17786", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of British Council's repayment of its pandemic loan on its ability to promote UK soft power.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746890, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17785", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to help ensure that people with Down Syndrome can receive direct payments from local councils.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746890", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746988, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17784", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of increases to employer National Insurance contributions at the Autumn Budget 2024 on (a) employment levels and (b) wages for (i) lower-paid and (ii) higher-paid", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746988", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746987, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17783", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of proposed increases to employer national insurance contributions on (a) full-time and (b) part-time workers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746987", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746986, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17782", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make a comparative assessment of the potential impact of (a) employment and (b) wage-level effects resulting from increases to employer National Insurance Contributions on (i) women and (ii) men.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746986", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746985, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17781", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an estimate of the total revenue to the public purse from increases in employer National Insurance Contributions for (a) GP practices, (b) dental practices, (c) hospices, (d) pharmacies and (e) othe", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746985", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746983, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17780", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral contribution by the Exchequer Secretary to the Treasury on 3 December 2024, Official Report, column 200, what estimate she has made of the (a) median and (b) mean average number of people ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746983", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746981, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17779", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the proportion of employers who will pay (a) the same and (b) less in employer National Insurance Contributions from April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746981", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746924, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17778", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what processes his Department has in place for Parliamentary oversight of Government decisions in (a) a time of war and (b) circumstances where the House of Commons is not functional.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746924", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746923, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17777", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will hold discussions with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on extending the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746923", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747090, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17776", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what performance reviews have been conducted on Capita\u2019s role in the recruitment of military personnel in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747089, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17775", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to publish a Command Paper on implementation of the Strategic Defence Review.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747085, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17774", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the role Capita's (a) systems and (b) processes played in the security failings that allowed Daniel Khalife to escape; and whether he plans to review Capita's contract with his Depa", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747085", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747077, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17773", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department is involved in the Serious Fraud Office\u2019s investigation into suspected bribery and corruption at Thales UK.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747077", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747075, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17772", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps whether he has made an assessment of the potential (a) legal and (b) financial implications for his Department of the Serious Fraud Office investigation into suspected bribery and corruption at Thales ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747075", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747074, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17771", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Thales products used by his Department are directly implicated in the Serious Fraud Office investigation into suspected bribery and corruption at that company.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747074", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747073, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17770", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Serious Fraud Office investigation into suspected bribery and corruption at Thales UK on defence procurement contracts with that company.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747073", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747064, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17769", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of (a) the participation of Mauritius in the Forum on China-Africa Cooperation and (b) sections on (i) military cooperat", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747064", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746956, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17768", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued on the circumstances in which registered sex offenders can apply to change their name.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746956", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746932, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17767", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 10 January 2024 to Question 7797 on Prisons: Research, what (a) conclusions she has drawn and (b) changes she has made as a result of the Ipsos MORI research project on the retribu", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746932", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746970, "askingMemberId": 1171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17766", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he expects the end of (a) animal testing and (b) testing on beagles at MBR Acres.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746970", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1747106, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17765", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to tackle gambling advertisements (a) online and (b) on television which are targeted at young people.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1747106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746947, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17764", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of working from home on civil service productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746947", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746938, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17763", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to prioritise domestic supply chains in defence procurement.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746938", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746951, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17762", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his planned timetable is for publishing a response to the Fairer Food Labelling consultation, which closed in May 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746951", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746927, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17761", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of increasing National Insurance contributions at the Autumn Budget 2024 on the ability of (a) Citizens Advice services and (b) other community-centred cha", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746927", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746671, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17760", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer,  with reference to her Department's policy paper, titled Changes to the Class 1 National Insurance Contributions Secondary Threshold, the Secondary Class 1 National Insurance contributions rate, and the Employment A", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746669, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17759", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of recycling precious metals found in (a) smartphones, (b) laptops and (c) other devices on the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Metals: Recycling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746669", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746672, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17758", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department\u2019s Get Britain Working White Paper published on 26 November 2024, whether the 140,000 places for Individual Placement and Support for severe mental illness are in ad", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Mental Illness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746699, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17757", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in the number of (a) adverse events and (b) rare side effects reported after receiving a covid-19 vaccine.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746696, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17756", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support local authorities that are facing challenges in managing people who have entered the UK illegally.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746674, "askingMemberId": 5360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17754", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce (a) the prevalence of money mules and (b) other financial exploitation.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746674", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746673, "askingMemberId": 5360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17753", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to make public spaces safer for women and girls in Hendon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Places: Hendon", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746729, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17752", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to increase the funding for services supporting victims of domestic abuse.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Victim Support Schemes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746729", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746728, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17751", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department plans to provide to help prevent (a) domestic abuse and (b) sexist and misogynistic attitudes that underpin domestic violence in the next financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746728", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746727, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17750", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of supported lodgings in supporting the aims of the Staying Close programme.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Care Leavers: Supported Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746727", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746726, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17749", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of  the merits of ensuring that the Staying Close programme is accessible to all Looked After Children.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Care Leavers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746726", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746725, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17748", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which authority is responsible for the recovery and disposal of boats that have sunk or are stranded near the shoreline when they do not present a navigation hazard.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Boats: Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746725", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746703, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17747", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of parent-delivered early language interventions for young children with Down Syndrome.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children: Down's Syndrome", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746702, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17746", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of embedding (a) social and (b) emotional learning interventions into curriculums.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Curriculum: Teaching Methods", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746701, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17745", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase collaborative working at local authority level to improve school attendance.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Attendance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746700, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17744", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to require building and health and safety standards in (a) emergency and (b) temporary accommodation provided to homeless families", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness: Temporary Accommodation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746698, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17743", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that homeless children have the same rights of access to (a) education and (b) health care as looked-after children in corporate parentship.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children's Rights: Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746697, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17742", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to help end child homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746679, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17741", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of (a) children of school age with complex SEND needs and (b) specialist educational places required for such children in the next five academic years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746678, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17740", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to encourage local authorities to plant more trees.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tree Planting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746678", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746677, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17739", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Israeli counterpart to lift the ban on journalists reporting from Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Journalism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746724, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17738", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of a devolution deal for Cornwall that does not involve any other regions or counties in the South West.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Devolution: Cornwall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746724", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746723, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17737", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of a devolved Cornish assembly.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Devolution: Cornwall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746723", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746722, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17736", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to help prevent international puppy smuggling.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dogs: Smuggling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746722", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746721, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17735", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many sewage discharges into (a) rivers and (b) seas have occurred so far this year in Cornwall.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sewage: Cornwall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746721", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746676, "askingMemberId": 5348, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17734", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential eligibility of Hemel Hempstead for the Respect Order pilot scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746720, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17733", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how will industry investment play a role in the development of autonomous offensive and defensive cyber tooling for the purpose of (a)  national security and (b) defence.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cybersecurity: Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746720", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746719, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17732", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the press release entitled UK and its allies must stay one step ahead in new AI arms race, published on 25 November 2024, how will the Laboratory for AI Sec", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Laboratory for AI Security Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746719", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746718, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17731", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the press release entitled UK and its allies must stay one step ahead in new AI arms race, published on 25 November 2024, where will the headquarters for th", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Laboratory for AI Security Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746717, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17730", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the press release entitled UK and its allies must stay one step ahead in new AI arms race, published on 25 November 2024, what his planned timetable is for ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Laboratory for AI Security Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746716, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17729", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the press release entitled UK and its allies must stay one step ahead in new AI arms race, published on 25 November 2024, whether the Ministry of Defence wi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746715, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17728", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the press release entitled UK and its allies must stay one step ahead in new AI arms race, published on 25 November 2024, whether the Laboratory for AI Secu", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746714, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17727", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the press release entitled UK and its allies must stay one step ahead in new AI arms race, published on 25 November 2024, which Department will have respons", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746713, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17726", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the press release entitled UK and its allies must stay one step ahead in new AI arms race, published on 25 November 2024, how will industry investment play ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Laboratory for AI Security Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746712, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17725", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to support the development of cyber capabilities within the defence sector through partnerships with UK (a) micro, (b) small and (c) medium-sized technology companies.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746711, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17724", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve engagement with UK (a) micro, (b) small and (c) medium-sized technology companies through traditional prime contractors.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746710, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17723", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how collaboration with (a) Ukrainian and (b) Israeli (i) hardware and (ii) software technology companies in the defence sector is informing the Strategic Defence Review.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Israel and Ukraine: Defence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746709, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17722", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to collaborate with Israeli (a) hardware and (b) software technology companies in the defence sector; and what lessons he has learned from that collaboration..", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Israel: Defence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746708, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17721", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to collaborate with Ukrainian (a) hardware and (b) software technology companies in the defence sector; and what lessons he has learned from that collaboration.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ukraine: Defence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746675, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17720", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of providing free covid-19 vaccinations for carers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746675", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746670, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17719", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to her Department's policy paper,  Changes to the Class 1 National Insurance Contributions Secondary Threshold, the Secondary Class 1 National Insurance contributions rate, and the Employment Allowanc", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746685, "askingMemberId": 5332, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17718", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will accept Ambitious about Autism\u2019s invitation to meet their Youth Network.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young People: Autism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746684, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17717", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he is taking steps to support small businesses with flood damage (a) prevention and (b) mitigation.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Floods", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746683, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17716", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to collaborate with local authorities to ensure that infrastructure is swiftly repaired after the recent floods.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Floods: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746682, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17715", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that early education and care providers are adequately supported to provide places for 70,000 more children by autumn 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childcare and Pre-school Education: Admissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746691, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17714", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of Professor Mary Renfrew's report entitled Enabling Safe Quality Midwifery Services and Care In Northern Ireland, publish", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746695, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17713", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the operating costs were for (a) HMNB Clyde and (b) RNAD Coulport for the most recent financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Clyde Naval Base and RNAD Coulport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746694, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17712", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) name, (b) purpose, (c) expected in-service date and (d) forecasted cost to the public purse is for all infrastructure projects within the Clyde Infrastructure programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Clyde Naval Base", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746693, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17711", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there are any planned infrastructure projects at (a) HMNB Clyde and (b) RNAD Coulport that do not fall within the Clyde Infrastructure Programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Clyde Naval Base and RNAD Coulport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746706, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17710", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to maintain the Mental Health Investment Standard.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746705, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17709", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of NHS funding has been allocated to mental health services in each year since 2015; and whether this funding met the NHS mental health investment standard.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746704, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17708", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of extra NHS funding announced at the budget will be allocated to NHS mental health services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746686, "askingMemberId": 5298, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17707", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to improve training for teachers to support pupils with special educational needs and disabilities in (a) mainstream and (b) specialist education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746689, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17706", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he plans to review the noise limits for onshore wind turbines defined in the ETSU-R-97 guidance, in the context of (a) advancements in onshore wind turbine technology and (b) evidence", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Wind Power: Noise", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746689", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746681, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17705", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to (a) reopen and (b) create new (i) Sustainable Farming Incentives and (ii) capital grants to replace previous ones  for (A) herbal lays, (B) fencing and ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746680, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17704", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of extending the Farming Resilience Fund beyond March 2025, in the context of phasing out the Basic Payment Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746707, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17703", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of standing down the Guard Force in Northern Ireland on the security of Army Reserve Centres; and what plans he has to support affected full-time re", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence Guard Service: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746690, "askingMemberId": 5259, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17702", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve maternity services in Leicestershire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Maternity Services: Leicestershire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746688, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17701", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish a learning disability strategy that includes measures on (a) health, (b) housing, (c) social care and (d) employment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Learning Disability: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746687, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17700", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential risks of omitting people with learning disabilities from the (a) 2025 and (b) spring 2026 covid-19 booster vaccination programme.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746477, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17699", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will have discussions with representatives of (a) NHS England and (b) other departmental bodies on the use of the term global majority in departmental (i) publications and (ii) internal docum", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department of Health and Social Care: Publications", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746663, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17698", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has had discussions with producer organisations on (a) the closure of the Fruit and Vegetable Aid Scheme and (b) replacing that scheme (i) in part or (ii) in ful", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Subsidies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746663", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746662, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17697", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's timetable is for making a decision on whether to extend the Fruit and Vegetable Aid Scheme beyond 31 December 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Subsidies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746662", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746661, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17696", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the Fruit and Vegetables Aid scheme beyond 31 December 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Subsidies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746661", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746590, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17695", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an assessment of the adequacy of public funding for Devon Hospiccare in Exeter.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospiscare: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746590", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746587, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17694", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will  make an assessment of the current adequacy of (a) regulation of fipronil and imidacloprid products, (b) (i) methods and (ii) scale of publication and promotion ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pets: Insecticides", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746587", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746487, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17693", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to expedite the establishment of the Supported Housing Advisory Panel.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Supported Housing: Advisory Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746484, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17692", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policies of the occupancy rate for houses in Watchet in Tiverton and Minehead constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Watchet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746483, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17691", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has had recent discussions with adult social care providers on the planned level of funding for the (a) NHS and (b) social care in the next four financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS and Social Services: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746593, "askingMemberId": 5232, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17690", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to increase the availability of practical driving tests in Blackpool North and Fleetwood constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746593", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746486, "askingMemberId": 5232, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17689", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle the practice of off-rolling.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746592, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17688", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 15981 on Gatwick Airport, whether the previous Secretary of State for Transport met with representatives of Gatwick Airport to discuss the proposed expansio", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746592", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746575, "askingMemberId": 5216, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17687", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help ensure equality of access to NHS services in the context of increases in digital patient-facing systems.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Digital Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746575", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746583, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "17686", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has consulted with all local schools in the Perranporth area as part of the review of the Perranporth Academy project; and when she expects the review to be concluded.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746583", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746578, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17685", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled REview24, published by the Association for Renewable Energy and Clean Technology on 14 November 2024, what steps he plans to take to tackle the po", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746578", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746664, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17684", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to invest in the recruitment and retention of radiologists in the Buckinghamshire, Oxfordshire and Berkshire West Integrated Care Board.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Radiology: Labour Turnover and Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746664", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746521, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17683", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she plans to take to (a) end homelessness and (b) involve people who have lived experience of homelessness in that process.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746581, "askingMemberId": 5199, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17682", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to improve the frequency of cancer statistics releases.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Statistics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746581", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746490, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17681", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the change in (a) core spending power and (b) settlement funding for (i) Aylesbury Vale District Council in each financial year between 2010-11 and ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance: Bedfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746622, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17680", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the recall rate was for offenders released under the End of Custody Supervised License scheme between October 2023 and June 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746622", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746621, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17679", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison places have been added to the estate since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746621", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746620, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17678", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the forecasted cost to the public purse was of adding 20,000 places to the prison estate (a) in total and (b) per place in October 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746620", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746619, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17677", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) total cost and (b) cost for each new prison place was for the Prison Estate Transformation Programme between 2016 and 2019.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746619", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746476, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17676", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has been provided use of a vehicle for official Ministerial travel from outside the Government Car Service.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Official Cars", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746573, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17675", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what national framework contractors have been appointed for flood management; and how and on what criteria they were appointed.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746573", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746646, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17674", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the procurement references are of current contracts related to the housing of irregular migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746646", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746645, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17673", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what services related to irregular migration work is undertaken by (a) contracted companies and (b) staff of her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746645", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746644, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17672", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of a consultation process with local residents before (a) a hotel and (b) other accommodation is used to house irregular migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Temporary Accommodation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746644", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746643, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17671", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 2 December 2024 to Question 15393 on Undocumented Migrants: Hotels, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of publishing a breakdown of the Asylum Accommodati", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Hotels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746643", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746642, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17670", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December to question 16316 on Department for Energy Security and Net Zero: Energy if he will publish data on each Department's energy use, broken down by en", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746642", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746640, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17669", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the answer of 2 December 2024 to Question 15704 on Jobcentres and Universal Credit: Telephone Services, what the costs were to her Department of translation and interpretation for each langu", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Jobcentres and Universal Credit: Telephone Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746640", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746638, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17668", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December to Question 15294 on Undocumented Migrants: Public Opinion, if she will publish all polling results the Department holds on public opinion regarding irregular migr", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Public Opinion", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746638", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746637, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17667", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December to Question 15294 on Undocumented Migrants: Public Opinion, if she will publish a breakdown of (a) companies contracted by the Department for polling on irregular ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Public Opinion", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746637", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746633, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17666", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an estimate of the number of migrants processed at Manston Immigration Centre without biometric system support since February 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Manston Asylum Processing Centre: Biometrics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746633", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746626, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17665", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what biometric system failures there were at UK borders in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration Controls: Biometrics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746626", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746635, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17664", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of workforce shortages on the delivery of palliative care services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palliative Care: Vacancies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746635", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746555, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17663", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will review the criteria for vehicle tax exemptions for disabled individuals (a) over the state pension age and (b) in receipt of Attendance Allowance.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disability: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746555", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746634, "askingMemberId": 5145, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17662", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that veterinary agreement concluded with the European Union reflects existing animal welfare protections.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterinary Services: UK Trade with EU", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746634", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746647, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17661", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve support for children with special educational needs and disabilities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746647", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746485, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17660", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to mandate food waste reporting.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Waste", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746641, "askingMemberId": 5135, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17659", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the classification of ketamine as a Class B drug under the Misuse of Drugs Act 1971; and if she will make an assessment of the potential merits o", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ketamine", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746641", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746488, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17658", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure the financial stability of the British Council.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Council: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746502, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17657", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of (a) NHS dentists and (b) NHS dental appointments in Stratford-on-Avon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746571, "askingMemberId": 5115, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17656", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people on zero-hours contracts in High Peak constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746571", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746558, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17655", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of replacing Police and Crime Commissioners with police panels.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police and Crime Commissioners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746558", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746557, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17654", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, If she will have discussions with the Police and Crime Commissioner for Devon, Cornwall and the Isles of Scilly on the adequacy of the system for appointing a Chief Constable for Devon and Cornwall Po", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Devon and Cornwall Police: Public Appointments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746557", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746556, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17653", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will take steps to ensure post offices cannot be closed without seeking the views of local residents.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Post Offices: Closures", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746556", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746553, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17652", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the written Statement of 5 November 2024 on Post Office Update, HCWS184, what work the external consultants have done; and what account the Parliamentary Under-Secretary for Business ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Post Office", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746553", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746507, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17651", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing an independent parking regulator.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746632, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17650", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to meet regularly with the Cambridgeshire and Peterborough Integrated Care Board; and whether he plans to issue guidance to the Board on the the construction of a town ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS Cambridgeshire and Peterborough", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746632", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746616, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17649", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when applications for the Infected Blood Compensation Scheme will open to those infected after the cut-off date of 1991.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746616", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746552, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17648", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason he has maintained the cut-off dates for the Infected Blood Compensation Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infected Blood Compensation Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746552", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746505, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17647", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential implications for (a) her policies and (b) the labour market of changes in the level of the provision of maths in universities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mathematics: Higher Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746504, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17646", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of maths provision in universities as part of the plan to recruit 6,500 new teachers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mathematics: Higher Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746580, "askingMemberId": 5091, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17645", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which countries have had visitor visas reinstated since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Overseas Visitors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746580", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746489, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17644", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has made a recent assessment with Cabinet colleagues of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals on regulating the use of AI in the context of food bios", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Disease Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746471, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17643", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has had discussions with the (a) Cabinet colleagues, (b) local authorities and (c) water companies on the potential impact of the proposed Universal Studios theme par", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Studios: Bedfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746470, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17642", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he plans to take to monitor the potential impact of the introduction of VAT on independent school fees on service families in receipt of the continuity of education allowance.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Private Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746469, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17641", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to provide additional support through the continuity of education allowance to help service families receiving the allowance with the cost of VAT on independent school fees.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Private Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746516, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17640", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many individuals on the prison estate are serving sentences for protest-related offences under (a) section (i) 12 and (ii) 14 of the Public Order Act 1986, as amended by section 75 of the Police, Crime, Sente", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Protest", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746512, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17639", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, how many prosecutions for protest-related offences the Crown Prosecution Service has completed under (a) section (i) 12 and (ii) 14 of the Public Order Act 1986, as amended by section 75 of the Police, Crime, Sentencing and C", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Demonstrations: Prosecutions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746639, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17638", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 16313 on Domestic Waste: Waste Disposal, what support is available to borough councils  to meet their obligation to provide food w", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Waste: Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746639", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746636, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17637", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 16313 on Domestic Waste: Waste Disposal, what steps he is taking to raise public awareness of the role of householders in forthcom", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Waste: Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746636", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746623, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17636", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2024 to Question 16313 on Domestic Waste: Waste Disposal, what his planned timetable is for Government to issue payments to local councils to procu", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746623", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746615, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17635", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data his Department holds on the provision of vision rehabilitation support in England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visual Impairment: Rehabilitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746615", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746551, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17634", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much base funding she plans to provide for (a) domestic abuse and sexual violence and (b) drugs and alcohol services in Torbay constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rehabilitation and Victim Support Schemes: Torbay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746551", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746534, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17633", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress her Department has made on helping to improve Great Western Railway services on Sundays.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Great Western Railway: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746527, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17632", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing vision rehabilitation services under the same (a) regulatory and (b) monitoring regimes as other adult social care serv", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visual Impairment: Rehabilitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746510, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17631", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to secure shared use agreements between schools and councils.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746500, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17630", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in Telford consistency claimed pension credit in November (a) 2022, (b) 2023 and (c) 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746599, "askingMemberId": 4938, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17629", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the relocation of the North Birmingham Urgent Treatment Centre to Sutton Coldfield is intended to be permanent; and what steps his Department plans to take to ensure equitable healthcare ac", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Birmingham Erdington", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746599", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746598, "askingMemberId": 4938, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17628", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether any consultation took place between the Birmingham and Solihull Integrated Care System and (a) local stakeholders, (b) elected officials, (c) the police and (d) community organisations prio", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Urgent Treatment Centres: Birmingham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746598", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746597, "askingMemberId": 4938, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17627", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to to help establish alternative urgent care facilities in Birmingham Erdington constituency, in the context of the emergency relocation of the North Birmingham Urgent ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Urgent Treatment Centres: Birmingham Erdington", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746597", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746596, "askingMemberId": 4938, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17626", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to take steps to help mitigate the impact of increased travel requirements for patients following the relocation of the North Birmingham Urgent Treatment Centre to Good", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Urgent Treatment Centres: Birmingham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746596", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746595, "askingMemberId": 4938, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17625", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the emergency relocation of the North Birmingham Urgent Treatment Centre to Good Hope Hospital on patient access to urgent treatment services ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Urgent Treatment Centres: Birmingham Erdington", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746595", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746668, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17624", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the potential impact of the Advertising (Less Healthy Food Definitions and Exemptions) Regulations 2024 to (a) por", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746668", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746660, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17623", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, on what dates the Minister for Investment has met with representatives from Stellantis since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746660", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746659, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17622", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, on what dates the Minister for Services, Small Business and Exports has met with representatives from Stellantis since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746659", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746577, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17621", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, on what dates he has met with representatives of Stellantis since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746577", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746522, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17620", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, on what dates the Minister for Industry has met with representatives from Stellantis since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746495, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17619", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on how many (a) abattoirs and (b) food processing plants in (i) England and (ii) the UK are family-owned businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Processed Food and Slaughterhouses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746515, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17618", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with her counterparts in the Greek Government on (a) loaning and (b) donating the Elgin Marbles to Greece.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746497, "askingMemberId": 4806, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17617", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to respond to the suggested guidance on single-sex spaces in the NHS drafted by the Darlington Nurses Union.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Gender", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746589, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17616", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has discussed the attack on the Iber Lepenci water canal in Kosovo with the Foreign Ministers of (a) the EU, (b) the USA, (c) France, (d) Italy and (e) Germany.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746589", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746588, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17615", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will increase the number of British military personnel deployed to KFOR following the attack on the Iber Lepenci water canal on 28 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746588", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746586, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17614", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when his Department last discussed the Banjska attack with the Serbian Government.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746586", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746585, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17613", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of the attack on the Iber Lepenci water canal in Kosovo on 28 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746585", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746584, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17612", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had discussions with his Kosovan counterpart on the attack on the Iber Lepenci water canal on 28 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746584", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746614, "askingMemberId": 4790, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17611", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of reports of sexual and gender-based violence in Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746614", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746613, "askingMemberId": 4790, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17610", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of reports of sexual and gender-based violence being committed by Israeli forces against Palestinia", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Israel: Palestinians", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746613", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746612, "askingMemberId": 4790, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17609", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether the Government has taken steps to provide aid to survivors of sexual and gender-based violence in Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746612", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746611, "askingMemberId": 4790, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17608", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether the Government has taken steps to provide aid to survivors of sexual and gender-based violence in Palestine.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palestinians: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746611", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746610, "askingMemberId": 4790, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17607", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2024 to Question 11671 on Lord Walney, whether she has discussed with Lord Walney (a) his role as the Independent Adviser on Political Violence and Disruption, (b)", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746610", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746607, "askingMemberId": 4790, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17606", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2024 to Question 11671 on Lord Walney, whether Lord Walney is participating in the review of the role of the Independent Adviser on Political Violence and Disrupti", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746607", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746606, "askingMemberId": 4790, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17605", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2024 to Question 11671 on Lord Walney, whether Lord Walney (a) has been since 5 July 2024 and (b) is the Independent Adviser on Political Violence and Disruption w", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746606", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746603, "askingMemberId": 4790, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17604", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of no recourse to public funds rules on migrant survivors of violence against women and girls.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Migrants: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746603", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746511, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17603", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claimants of (a) Universal Credit, (b) Employment Support Allowance, (c) Personal Independence Payment, (d) Jobseeker's Allowance and (e) income support had (i) Level", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746591, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17602", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will take steps to ensure that private firms do not profit from out of area looked after children's residential care placements.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Care Homes: Profits", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746591", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746561, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17601", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a housing ombudsman service for the private sector.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Private Sector", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746560, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17600", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to tackle rural homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746560", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746559, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17599", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to tackle the underlying causes of homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746559", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746520, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17598", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to support women in the engineering sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Engineering: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746519, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17597", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make assessment of the adequacy of diagnosis times for endometriosis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Endometriosis: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746518, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17596", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of having an awareness raising campaign on endometriosis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Endometriosis: Health Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746517, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17595", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of having an awareness raising campaign for NHS clinicians on endometriosis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Endometriosis: Health Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746496, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17594", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of having a single construction regulator.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Construction: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746493, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17593", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to issue guidance to local authorities on awarding contracts to companies responsible for the 2017 Grenfell fire.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746492, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17592", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the penalties will be for landlords who do not follow the Remediation Acceleration Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "High Rise Flats: Insulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746609, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17591", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families in Slough constituency have been affected by the two-child benefit cap in each year since 2017.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Child Benefit: Slough", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746609", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746601, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17590", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support policing in Anguilla.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Anguilla", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746601", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746600, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17589", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of GP surgeries are rated as (a) outstanding and (b) good by the Care Quality Commission in Slough constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Slough", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746600", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746594, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17588", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps she has taken to reduce homelessness in (a) Slough constituency and (b) Thames Valley region.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746594", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746576, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17587", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps is she taking increase school attendance among children who are living in poverty.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupils: Attendance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746576", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746501, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17586", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the APPG report entitled Deaths Abroad, Consular Services and Assistance Report 2019: Why families in the UK deserve better and what can be done, whether hi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Nationals Abroad: Death", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746549, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17584", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she has had recent discussions with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on taking steps to prevent people being sexually exploited on websites advertising prostitution in Gower constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostitution: Gower", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746549", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746526, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17583", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department holds data on Welsh prisoners by (a) sex, (b) ethnicity, (c) socio-economic background, (d) offence type, (e) sentence type and (f) local authority.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746523, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17582", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department holds data on the number of Welsh people in the prison system.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746479, "askingMemberId": 4617, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17581", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Apulia G7 Leaders\u2019 communique, published in June 2024, what steps his Department is taking to support civil society peacebuilding efforts in (a) Israel ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Israel: Palestinians", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746568, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17580", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how safeguarding the Best and Most Versatile agricultural land will be taken into account when she considers the Highsted Park development.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Garden Communities: Sittingbourne", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746568", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746567, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17579", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how the commitment to safeguard the Best and Most Versatile agricultural land is applied to planning decisions.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Land", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746567", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746566, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17578", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to safeguard the Best and Most Versatile agricultural land.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Land", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746566", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746565, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17577", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how she plans to report on the effectiveness of her  safeguarding of the Best and Most Versatile agricultural land in line with the National Planning Policy Framework.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Land", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746565", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746564, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17576", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will publish how many hectares of the Best and Most Versatile agricultural land are (a) protected, (b) under consideration for development and (c) approved for consent in ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Land", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746564", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746563, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17575", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason she called in Highsted Park outline planning applications 21/503906/EIOUT and 21/503914/EIOUT.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Garden Communities: Sittingbourne", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746563", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746562, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17574", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what criteria she uses to call in planning applications before they are discussed by local councillors.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746513, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17573", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an estimate of the potential impact of the \u00a3240 million funding allocated to her Department in the Autumn Budget 2024 for trialling new ways of getting people back into work on savings ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Schemes: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746480, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17572", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the differences are between the (a) Connect to Work and (b) Universal support schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Connect to Work and Universal Support", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746649, "askingMemberId": 4500, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17571", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to prevent insurers underwriting fossil fuel projects.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746649", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746648, "askingMemberId": 4500, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17570", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of whether the divestment of pension funds from insurance companies that are not compliant with the UK\u2019s climate commitments is a part of fiduciary duty.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746648", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746667, "askingMemberId": 4493, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17569", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what level her Department will raise the living standards of those struggling to meet their basic needs by 2030; and if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure a statutory commitment to a", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746667", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746618, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17568", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what her Department's timetable is for responding to the National Planning Policy Framework consultation that ended on 24 September 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746618", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746548, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17567", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.43 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, whether she has made an estimate of the average difference in the business rate bill of a hereditament eligible for r", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitality Industry and Leisure: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746548", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746547, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17566", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department made an assessment of the potential impact of calling in the planning application for the proposed Chinese Embassy in Tower Hamlets on (a) diplomatic, (b) ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746547", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746546, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17565", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, (a) when and (b) how her Department became aware of the new planning application for the proposed new Chinese Embassy near the Tower of London.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746546", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746545, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17564", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many affordable homes were (a) started and (b) completed in England between 2010-11 and 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746545", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746544, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17563", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how the planning application for the proposed Chinese Embassy near the Tower of London differs from the previous planning application for the Embassy turned down by the London Bo", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746544", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746543, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17562", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what formula her Department plans to use to determine (a) which local authorities will receive funding from the Recovery Grant and (b) the amount of such funding allocated to eac", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746543", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746542, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17561", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when she plans to publish the provisional local government finance settlement for financial year 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746542", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746541, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17560", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 28 November 2024 on Local Government Finance, HCWS265, whether her Department has carried out an equality impact assessment on repurpos", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746541", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746540, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17559", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many local authority officers are seconded to her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Secondment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746540", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746538, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17558", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will (a) take steps to allow local authorities to set unlimited fines for littering and fly-tipping offences and (b) make an assessment of the financial resources local authority", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fly Tipping and Litter: Fines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746537, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department's consultation entitled Enabling remote attendance and proxy voting at local authority meetings, published on 24 October 2024, what assessment sh", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Remote Working", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746535, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17556", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of Local Plans have been withdrawn by local authorities in 2024 following advice from the Planning Inspectorate; and what assessment she has made of the financial", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Plans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746533, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17555", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of appeal hearings considered by the Planning Inspectorate were conducted virtually in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning: Appeals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746532, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17554", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will publish guidance for local authorities on four day working weeks and annualised hours.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Working Hours", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746531, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17553", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the impact of the Housing (Right to Buy) (Limits on Discount) (England) Order 2024 on levels of home ownership.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Ownership", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746529, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17552", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact the planned increase in employer National Insurance contributions on external services commissioned by local government.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746528, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17551", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to increase scrutiny arrangements in mayoral combined authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Combined Authorities: Accountability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746605, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17550", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much of the NHS funding announced in the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, will be allocated to ambulance services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ambulance Services: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746605", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746604, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17549", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending NHS Outer London Weighting to (a) Hertsmere and (b) Watford.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: London Allowance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746604", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746602, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17548", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will increase the staffing budget for the East of England Ambulance Service.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "East of England Ambulance Service NHS Trust: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746602", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746550, "askingMemberId": 4439, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17547", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the performance trajectory of CrossCountry Trains following the implementation of its reduced timetable.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746550", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746554, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17546", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of recent reports of the Zamzam displacement camp in Sudan being shelled by Rapid Support Forces.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746554", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746474, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17545", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for which public appointments the Prime Minister is directly responsible.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prime Minister: Public Appointments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746608, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17544", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) economic impact of the bluetongue restrictions on affected farmers and (b) animal health impact of the bluetongue restriction.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bluetongue Disease", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746608", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746514, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17543", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to facilitate an inward visit to the UK from former President of Taiwan, Tsai Ing-wen.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tsai Ing-wen", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746506, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17542", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of Russian interference in the upcoming Ghanaian general election.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746475, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17540", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, , what discussions he has had with the incoming US administration to secure the release of hostages held by Hamas in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Hostage Taking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746473, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17539", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact on charity lotteries of introducing a statutory levy on gambling operators.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gambling: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746472, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17538", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to publish research commissioned by her department to gather evidence about the (a) size and (b) nature of the prize draw sector.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prize Money: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746498, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17537", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending food labelling legislation so that sourcing information of ingredients is required on pre-packed food and drink produ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Labelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746509, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17536", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on reviewing powers of entry for social workers.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Workers: Powers of Entry", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746508, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17535", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she plans to review legal protections around the (a) abuse and (b) neglect of older people.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Violence: Older People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746482, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17534", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason (a) women are paid of \u00a3985 per cycle for their eggs and (b) men are paid \u00a345 per donation for their sperm.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "IVF: Payments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746481, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17533", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has commissioned research into the potential long-term health impact on young women's bodies of egg retrieval.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "IVF: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746494, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17532", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November to Question 13473 and the Answer of 20 November 2024 to Question 14457 and 16158 on London North Eastern Railway: WiFi, what proportion of complaints about facilities on bo", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746666, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17531", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the (a) chemicals and (b) plastics sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746666", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746658, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17530", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the aerospace sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746658", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746657, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17529", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the automotive sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746657", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746656, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17528", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill on the advanced manufacturing sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746656", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746655, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17527", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, on what dates the (a) Minister for Employment Rights, Competition and Markets and (b) Minister for Trade Policy and Economic Security has met with representatives from Stellantis.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746655", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746628, "askingMemberId": 4020, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17526", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether his Department plans to measure the private sector investment in the research and development economy by (a) sector, (b) cluster and (c) departmental spend.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Research: Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746628", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746665, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17525", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to financially support the South Atlantic Medal Association.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "South Atlantic Medal Association", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746665", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746569, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17524", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the non-standard occupation groups in his Department are.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746569", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746536, "askingMemberId": 1466, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17523", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many wet cargo ships have been boarded by UK authorities in territorial waters for lacking insurance this year.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Merchant Shipping: Insurance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746631, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17522", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department's consultation entitled Proposed reforms to the National Planning Policy Framework and other changes to the planning system, updated 24 September", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning: Derelict Land", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746631", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746630, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17521", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department's consultation entitled Proposed reforms to the National Planning Policy Framework and other changes to the planning system, updated 24 September", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning: Reform", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746630", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746629, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17520", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department will announce future funding for drug treatment services beyond 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Drugs: Rehabilitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746629", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746627, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17519", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce barriers to accessing drug treatment faced by women.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Drugs: Rehabilitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746627", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746625, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17518", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support the Church of England in maintaining its built heritage.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Church of England: Buildings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746625", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746624, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17517", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she has taken to support listed places of worship.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746624", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746617, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17516", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what changes to procedures she has made following the investigation by law enforcement agencies into fraudulent transactions made on the Royal Mint website since 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746617", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746582, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17515", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he plans to raise the (a) declaration of martial law in South Korea and (b) potential implications of that decision at the UN.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746582", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746574, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17514", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.40 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of (a) the increase in the rate of employers' National Insuran", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746574", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746539, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17513", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how much he plans to allocate to the World Bank Group International Development Association replenishment fund in the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "International Development Association: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746539", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746530, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17512", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an estimate of the number of electric vehicle charging points there will be in each year from 2025 to 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Charging Points", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746491, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17511", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2024 to question 16452 Living Wage Living Wage, what the average number of hours worked by those in part-time employment and who paid the National Living Wage was i", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746579, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17510", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the police allocation formula on (a) policing and (b) crime in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746579", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746572, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17509", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has made an assessment of the impact of the accelerated energy grid decarbonisation target on the UK's reliance on imports from China.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Imports: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746572", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746570, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17508", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what the cost to the public purse was of the UK delegation's participation in COP29 in Baku.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Climate Change Convention: Azerbaijan", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746570", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746525, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17507", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer on 26 November to Question 14583 on Veterans: Radiation Exposure, if he will set a deadline for the publication of his Department's internal review into the whereabouts of nuclear test vete", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Radiation Exposure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746524, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17506", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the anticipated total cost of compensation for legal claims brought by Nuclear Test Veterans.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Radiation Exposure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746503, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17505", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what the total cost to the public purse of curtailment of onshore wind turbines in England was in the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Wind Power: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746654, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17504", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make a an assessment of the effectiveness of the distribution of quota between (a) foreign and (b) domestic-owned trawlers under ten metres in the UK inshore fleet.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746654", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746653, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17503", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will (a) take steps to review the operation of the landing obligation and (b) publish the number of enforcement actions taken against vessels that have failed to comply with the ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746653", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746652, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17502", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish the opening positions for each Total Allowable Catch in the (a) EU/UK bilateral and (b) EU/UK/Norway trilateral negotiations.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746652", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746651, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17501", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many vessels are taking part in the early adopter phase of the remote electronic monitoring rollout by having cameras installed; and what steps he is taking to increase the number ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746651", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746650, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "17500", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish measures for the remaining offshore Marine Protected Areas (MPAs) under stage (a) 3 and (b) 4 of the Marine Management Organisation's offshore MPA process.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746650", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746395, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17499", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has had recent discussions with representatives of migrant organisations on the development of a digital solution for the e-visa scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Digital Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746395", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746394, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17498", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the e-Visa scheme on (a) older people, (b) those with learning difficulties, (c) non-English speakers and (d) those with limited access to techn", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Digital Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746394", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746393, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17497", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to restore funding to the Career Change Programme.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746393", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746391, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17495", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of raising the bus cap to \u00a33 on pensioners.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746391", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746386, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17494", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether any parts of North Cornwall constituency will receive funding from the Recovery Grant announced by her Department on 28 November 2024; and what additional steps she is ta", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance: North Cornwall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746386", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746384, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17493", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of (a) extending the Future Farm Resilience Fund and (b) introducing any new schemes of monetary support for farms", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Farmers: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746384", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746390, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17491", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with the (a) Cabinet Office and (b) Department for Science, Innovation and Technology on the (i) development and (ii) procurement of digital capabilities for national secur", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Security: Cybersecurity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746390", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746389, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17490", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether frontier technologies such as (a) machine learning and (b) artificial intelligence are being used within (i) the Armed Forces and (ii) his Department to help improve workforce efficiencies.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces and Ministry of Defence: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746389", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746388, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17489", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to help train military personnel cyber warfare skills.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electronic Warfare: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746388", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746383, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17488", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the costs of maintaining (a) HMS Queen Elizabeth and (b) HMS Prince of Wales over the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Prince of Wales and HMS Queen Elizabeth", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746383", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746382, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17487", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his oral evidence of 21 November 2024 to the Defence Select Committee, HC 345, what steps he is taking to ensure the planned deployments of (a) HMS Queen Elizabeth and (b) HMS Prince of Wales ta", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Prince of Wales and HMS Queen Elizabeth", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746382", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746381, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17486", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the status is of each of the Royal Navy\u2019s Type 45 destroyers.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Type 45 Destroyers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746381", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746380, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17485", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with NATO allies on the potential impact of the retirement of naval assets on the UK's ability to contribute to NATO operations.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NATO: Navy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746380", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746379, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17484", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new Type (a) 45, (b) 26, (c) 31 and (d) 32 will enter service by 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Frigates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746379", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746378, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17483", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the expected timeline is for the Type 32 frigate programme to move from the concept phase to design and procurement.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Type 32 Frigates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746378", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746375, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17480", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of retiring (a) RFA Wave Knight and (b) RFA Wave Ruler on the Royal Navy's ability to support concurrent operations involving multiple carrier strike grou", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "RFA Wave Knight and RFA Wave Ruler", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746375", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746374, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17479", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the decision to retire (a) HMS Albion, (b) HMS Bulwark, (c) HMS Northumberland, (d) RFA Wave Knight and (e) RFA Wave Ruler on the (i) training an", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Navy and Royal Fleet Auxiliary: Decommissioning", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746374", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746370, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17475", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the UK's ability to form a fully operational Carrier Strike Group; and how often that Group could be deployed globally.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aircraft Carriers: Deployment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746369, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17474", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the projected annual operational cost savings are from the decommissioning of (a) RFA Wave Knight and (b) RFA Wave Ruler.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "RFA Wave Knight and RFA Wave Ruler", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746369", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746368, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17473", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the (a) cost of repairing and (b) savings from the early decommissioning of HMS Northumberland.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Northumberland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746368", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746367, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17472", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of reallocating funds from the decommissioning of HMS (a) Albion and (b) Bulwark to accelerate delivery of Multi-Role Support Ships.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Multi-role Ocean Surveillance Ships", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746367", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746366, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17471", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to his oral response of 26 November 2024, Official Report column 631, what the terms of reference are for the review of the enforcement of sanctions; who is co", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sanctions: Reviews", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746366", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746365, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17470", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to his oral contribution in response to the question from the hon. Member for Bicester and Woodstock on 26 November 2024, Official Report, column 631, what the", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Oil", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746365", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746213, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17462", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many projects in the Teesside carbon capture and storage cluster are (a) existing projects being retrofitted and (b) new developments.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carbon Capture and Storage: Tees Valley", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746283, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17461", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations has she received from religious organisations about extending the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme beyond March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746282, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17460", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the impact of recent NHS contract reforms on access to NHS dentistry in (a) West Dorset constituency and (b) other rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746252, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17459", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his  Department is taking to address shortages in NHS dentists in rural areas; and what his timeline is for tackling such gaps.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746252", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746251, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17458", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing additional incentives for NHS dentists to operate in (a) rural and (b) remote areas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746251", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746250, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17457", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps she has taken with cabinet colleagues to tailor homelessness prevention strategies for (a) West Dorset constituency and (b) other rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746250", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746249, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17456", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help provide accommodation for homeless people in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746249", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746248, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17455", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of changes in the level of living costs on homelessness rates; and what steps she is taking to mitigate tha", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746248", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746237, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17454", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with religious organisations on the potential impact of the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme on religious buildings.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746237", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746231, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17453", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals on requiring drugs manufacturers to include additional labelling on the front of boxes of", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Drugs: Labelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746231", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746229, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17452", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment has her department made of the potential impact of the operation of the new waste incinerator on Portland on public transport in West Dorset constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Transport: Portland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746229", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746228, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17451", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to secure funding for rural housing enablers to support housing initiatives in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746228", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746225, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17450", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to support rural business (a) innovation (b) and investment in (i) West Dorset constituency and (ii) similar areas.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rural Areas: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746225", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746224, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17449", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will take steps to ensure that trade agreements have a positive impact on the agricultural sector in West Dorset constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: Agriculture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746223, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17448", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will take steps to help reduce transportation costs for (a) goods and (b) services in rural economies.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746217, "askingMemberId": 5324, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17447", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of pressurised metered dose inhalers were manufactured in pharmaceutical production facilities (a) in the UK and (b) overseas in the last year for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asthma: Medical Equipment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746216, "askingMemberId": 5324, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17446", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many pressurised metered dose inhalers were prescribed by the NHS in the last year for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asthma: Medical Equipment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746159, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17445", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether legal costs associated with the case between the General Medical Council (GMC) and Anaesthetists United, regarding regulation of Physician and Anaesthesia Associates will be paid for by the", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anaesthesia Associates and Physician Associates: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746325, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17444", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on future funding arrangements for the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746325", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746227, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17443", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has had discussions with the Northern Ireland Executive on legislation on (a) leasehold and (b) freehold affecting properties in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746227", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746230, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17442", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of issuing guidance to prisons on supporting children in custody in different pandemic scenarios.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Offenders: Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746230", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746226, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17441", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care to develop a coordinated strategy for managing the health and wellbeing of children in custodial settings during future pandemics.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Offenders: Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746226", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746222, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17440", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce alcohol-specific deaths.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alcoholism: Death", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746221, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17439", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce death rates from (a) alcohol, (b) drugs and (c) suicide in (a) the North and (b) coastal regions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alcoholism and Drugs: Death", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746220, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17438", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to use evidence-based measures of community resilience for funding decisions.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Emergencies: Planning", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746219, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17437", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle regional inequalities in community resilience in the national resilience review.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Emergencies: Planning", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746215, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17436", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to ensure (a) teachers and (b) school staff have adequate (i) knowledge of and (ii) confidence in teaching autistic children.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Autism: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746168, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17435", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his speech to the 2024 Country Land and Business Association conference of 21 November 2024, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the pr", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746354, "askingMemberId": 5298, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17434", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2024 to Question 13971 on Financial Services: Euro, what steps her Department is taking to mitigate against the risk of the EU not extending its equivalence decision for UK cent", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Financial Services: Euro", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746354", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746342, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17433", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the review into the loan charge will include examining the roles of (a) scheme promoters, (b) umbrella companies and (c) tax advisers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tax Avoidance: Reviews", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746342", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746322, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17432", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to ensure the independence of the new review on the loan charge.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tax Avoidance: Reviews", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746322", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746302, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17431", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of abolishing the furnished holiday let tax regime on local (a) economies and (b) jobs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Holiday Accommodation: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746302", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746301, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17430", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of cooperative energy models.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746301", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746329, "askingMemberId": 5287, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17428", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of vaccine doses that are thrown away due to reaching their expiry date before they could be used.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vaccination: Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746329", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746287, "askingMemberId": 5286, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17427", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the policy paper entitled The Power of Music to Change Lives: A National Plan for Music Education, published by her Department on 25 June 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Music: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746233, "askingMemberId": 5286, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17426", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of reduced funding for (a) Now Teach and (b) other charities on the recruitment of teachers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746233", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746246, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17425", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of a time limit for claiming Council Tax exemption under Class F.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746246", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746324, "askingMemberId": 5282, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17424", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help support Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services (a) to reduce waiting times, (b) limit the rejection of referrals and (c) improve trust in services by both (i) p", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746324", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746238, "askingMemberId": 5282, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17423", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help prevent the closure of Post Office branches in (a) Chipping Barnet constituency and (b) the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Post Offices: Closures", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746238", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746267, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17422", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the number of employees who will be impacted by the closure of the Department\u2019s office in Truro; and what assessment she has made of the potential i", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Truro", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746192, "askingMemberId": 5278, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17420", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to incentivise private developers to build more (a) social and (b) affordable homes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746191, "askingMemberId": 5278, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17419", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of new social homes built across London; and what assessment she has made of the adequacy of funding for affordable hou", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746190, "askingMemberId": 5278, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17418", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to extend funding for independent, non-profit, specialist advice for families involved with the (a) child welfare and (b) family justice systems beyond March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Families: Advisory Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746306, "askingMemberId": 5270, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17417", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the maximum number of months for which the Bereavement Support Payment can be paid beyond the existing cap of 18 monthly payments.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746306", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746304, "askingMemberId": 5270, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17416", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to ensure that there is adequate (a) funding and (b) support for (i) forensic investigation teams and (ii) coroner services to help minimise delays.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746184, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17415", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of (a) the potential effectiveness of carbon capture technologies in reducing emissions and (b) whether investment in such technologies is the most (i) efficient a", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carbon Capture and Storage", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746169, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17414", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the guidance on meal deals in his Department\u2019s publication entitled Restricting promotions of products high in fat, sugar or salt by location and by volume price: implementation guidance, u", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Sales Promotions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746234, "askingMemberId": 5253, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17413", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps with the music industry to ensure performing artists have access to adequate mental health support.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Musicians: Mental Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746234", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746305, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17412", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report by Gingerbread entitled Fix the CMS, published on 25 November 2024, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) assigning (i) dedicated and (ii) named case", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Child Maintenance Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746305", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746182, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17411", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will meet the hon. member for Tiverton and Minehead and the Peninsula Rail Task Force.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: South West", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746181, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17410", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of exempting hospitality businesses from proposed changes to employer National Insurance contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitality Industry: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746180, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17409", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the record-keeping requirement for the Sustainable Farming Initiative for 2024 will be maintained.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sustainable Farming Incentive", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746179, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17408", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential impact of the Energy Performance Certificate on the ability of households to manage heating bills.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Performance Certificates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746178, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17407", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if his Department will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the use of heat pumps in (a) uninsulated and (b) improperly insulated homes.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heat Pumps", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746177, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17406", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if her Department will make an assessment of the adequacy of regulation on the duty of care transfer of vulnerable tenants from housing associations to village agents.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing Associations: Vulnerable Adults", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746176, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17405", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential impact of mechanical failure of Magna Air Source heat pumps in social housing on tenants.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Heat Pumps", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746174, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17403", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of further regulating social care micro-providers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Services: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746188, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17401", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking with local authorities to ensure that tied accommodation provided to seasonal agricultural workers meets the Housing Health and Safety Rating System stan", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Seasonal Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746187, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17400", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has made an assessment of the standard of accommodation provided to seasonal agricultural workers on UK farms in line with the Housing Health and Safety Rating System", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Seasonal Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746334, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17397", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what diplomatic steps his Department is taking to help protect human rights in the Balochistan region of Pakistan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Balochistan: Human Rights", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746334", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746348, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17394", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Autumn Budget 2024 on the (a) materials and (b) critical minerals sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Manufacturing Industries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746348", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746347, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17393", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Autumn Budget 2024 on the steel sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Iron and Steel: Manufacturing Industries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746347", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746346, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17392", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Autumn Budget 2024 on the (a) maritime and (b) shipbuilding sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shipbuilding and Shipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746346", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746345, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17391", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of Autumn Budget 2024 on the construction sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746345", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746210, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17390", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if her Department will take steps to ensure that communities receive required infrastructure upgrades before new houses are occupied in (a) Harpenden and Berkhamsted constituency", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Hertfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746209, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17389", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to protect the green belt in (a) Harpenden and Berkhamsted constituency, (b) Tring and (c) Dacorum, in the context of the consultation entitle", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Green Belt: Hertfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746193, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17388", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to introduce measures to improve patient safety in non-surgical cosmetic procedures.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Non-surgical Cosmetic Procedures: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746240, "askingMemberId": 5197, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17387", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to ensure that the Strategic Defence Review contains adequate funding for UK Space Command to deliver (a) on procurement and (b) operationally.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Space Command: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746240", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746236, "askingMemberId": 5197, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17386", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the next meeting is of the Space Council.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Space Council", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746236", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746183, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17382", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the letter of 1 August 2024 from the hon. Member for Yeovil on the closure of Yeovil District Hospital\u2019s hyper acute stroke unit.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746319, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17381", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of long-term health concerns associated with the use of 3-Nitrooxypropanol in cattle feed.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Feed: 3-nitrooxypropanol", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746319", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746310, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17380", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been deported (a) in total and (b) by nationality in each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deportation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746310", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746337, "askingMemberId": 5159, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17379", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of using electronic travel authorisations on the speed in which Hong Kong (a) BNO status holders and (b) political prisoners can leave H", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electronic Travel Authorisations: Hong Kong", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746337", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746316, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17377", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of Universal Credit claimants have a note on their record saying that an interpreter is required when her Department contacts them.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit: Interpreters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746316", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746313, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17376", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which external companies are contracted by the NHS to provide training for staff.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746313", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746312, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17375", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list all companies contracted by her Department to undertake work related to (a) irregular migration and (b) irregular migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746312", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746311, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17374", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list all contracted services undertaken by Serco related to irregular migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Serco: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746311", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746309, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17373", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse was of the provision of taxis for irregular migrants in each year since 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Taxis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746309", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746276, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17372", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of deploying naval assets to the English Channel to help tackle small boats crossing.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: English Channel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746274, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17371", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) churches (b) synagogues (c) mosques and (d) other places of worship were investigated for suspected ties to extremism in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Religious Buildings: Radicalism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746273, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17370", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish a breakdown of the conditions that need to be met for an person to be placed on the terror watchlist.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Terrorism: Surveillance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746272, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17369", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how individuals on the terror watchlist are monitored.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Terrorism: Surveillance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746271, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17368", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of individuals on the terror watchlist are (a) UK citizens, (b) Dual national citizens, (c) UK citizens with at least one non-UK parent and (d) non-UK citizens.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Terrorism: Surveillance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746270, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17367", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in how many years the ONS estimates on immigration to the UK been revised upwards in each of the last 20 years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Statistics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746269, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17366", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will conduct a review of the accuracy of the methodology used to collect immigration statistics.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Statistics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746268, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17365", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that Bovaer is not used within the school supply chain.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "School Meals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746266, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17364", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will review the use of Bovaer.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "3-nitrooxypropanol", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746265, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17363", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Minister of State for Border Security and Asylum will meet the hon. Member for Great Yarmouth to discuss data release policies.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746212, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17362", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of Covid-19 lockdowns on trends in people\u2019s quality-adjusted life years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Disease Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746211, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17361", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will provide a list of all contracted services from GTD Healthcare; and what the cost to the public purse of those services is.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "GTD Healthcare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746335, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17360", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of implementing measures to support pensioners whose defined benefit schemes are underfunded.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746335", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746333, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17359", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the financial status of people (a) who received pre-1997 defined benefit pensions and (b) who received payments from schemes with mandatory increases.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746333", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746332, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17358", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the number of retirees affected by the lack of statutory inflation protection for pre-1997 defined benefit pensions.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Workplace Pensions: Inflation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746332", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746331, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17357", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps with Cabinet colleagues to encourage private pension schemes to voluntarily offer inflation protection for pre-1997 defined benefit pension entitlements.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746331", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746330, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17356", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to address the lack of statutory inflation protection for pre-1997 defined benefit pension entitlements.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Workplace Pensions: Inflation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746330", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746328, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17355", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of regulations not subjecting pre-1997 defined benefit pensions to statutory indexation on the financial wellbeing of pensioners.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Workplace Pensions: Inflation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746328", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746198, "askingMemberId": 5152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17354", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether SEND schools will be exempt from proposed changes to charitable business rate relief.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746208, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17353", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, when he plans to implement sections (a) 61 to 65, (b) 67 (c) 70 to 74 and (d) other remaining provisions of the Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure Act 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure Act 2022", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746207, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17352", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of enquiries to Action Fraud were taken up in the latest period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Action Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746205, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17350", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of allowing local authorities to use automatic number plate recognition for car park management.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Parking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746204, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17349", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 79 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, which regions will receive funding from the \u00a32.4 billion allocated to the building of flood d", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746203, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17348", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make a comparative estimate of the cost per mile of new (a) busways, (b) ultra light rail and (c) conventional train systems.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Transport: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746202, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17347", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral statement entitled Rail Performance of 11 November 2024, Official Report, column 517, when she plans to issue a private train operating company with three months' notice that it will ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Train Operating Companies: Nationalisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746201, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17346", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what her planned timetable is to publish her Department's strategy on rolling stock procurement.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rolling Stock: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746200, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17345", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average waiting time was in weeks for a Driver Certificate of Professional Competence part 3b test in (a) England, (b) Central Bedfordshire and (c) each driving centre in November (i) 2024 and (ii) 202", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Large Goods Vehicle Drivers: Driving Tests", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746162, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17344", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what her Department\u2019s policy is on funding for Community Rail Partnerships, in the context of the Passenger Railway Services (Public Ownership) Act 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Railways Initiative: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746218, "askingMemberId": 5126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17342", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the budget allocation for the Animal and Plant Health Agency in Weybridge for the financial year 2025-26 is included within the \u00a3500 million uplift for agricultural spending fo", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746350, "askingMemberId": 5120, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17341", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) meet demand for radiation treatment and (b) reduce NHS waiting times for people with cancers that require urgent treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746350", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746339, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17339", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to help improve the quality of the service provided to passengers on South Western Railway.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "South Western Railway: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746339", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746338, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17338", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make it her policy to reverse fare increases introduced in 2024 on South Western Railway when it is brought into public ownership in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "South Western Railway: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746338", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746197, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17337", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2024 to Question 12890 on Department for Energy Security and Net Zero: Ministers\u2019 Private Offices, what items were purchased to equip the office of the additional Minister.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero: Ministers' Private Offices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746196, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17336", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2024 to Question 12890 on Department for Energy Security and Net Zero: Ministers\u2019 Private Offices, if she will published an itemised breakdown of that spending.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero: Ministers' Private Offices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746293, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17335", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what changes she expects to make to governance arrangements in Bedfordshire through the English Devolution White Paper.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Bedfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746292, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17334", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much she expects (a) Central Bedfordshire Council and (b) Bedford Borough Council to increase council tax in 2025/26.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax: Bedfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746290, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17333", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much she expects the non-Council Tax element of the core spending power of (a) Central Bedfordshire Council and (b) Bedford Borough Council to increase in 2025/26.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance: Bedfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746284, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17332", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to support people in areas of poor (a) broadband and (b) mobile phone signal during the switchover to digital alternatives to landlines.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Broadband and Mobile Phones: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746280, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17330", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential impact of train delays in (a) Q3 and (b) Q4 2024 on productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746279, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she plans to take to improve the reliability of train services.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746278, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with Thameslink on the performance of services on the Bedford Line.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Thameslink Line: Bedford", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746278", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746263, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17327", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2024 to Question 14160 on Higher Education: VAT, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of enabling groups of universities to share VAT-exempt costs at contr", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Higher Education: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746344, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of domestic cybersecurity risks on food biosecurity.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Cybersecurity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746344", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746343, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17324", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Geospatial Commission on research into food biosecurity.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746343", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746340, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17323", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many CH-47 Chinook helicopters have been deployed in Operations overseas in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinook Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746340", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746245, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17322", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to produce a domestic research strategy for food biosecurity.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746245", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746244, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17321", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the domestic opportunities through Horizon Europe for research into food biosecurity.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746244", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746243, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17320", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with Research England on their approach to support for research into food biosecurity since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746243", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746242, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17319", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with Innovate UK on research into food biosecurity since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746242", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746241, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17318", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with the Science and Technology Facilities Council on research into food biosecurity since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746241", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746239, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17317", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with the Natural Environment Research Council on research into food biosecurity since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746239", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746235, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17316", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with the Medical Research Council on research into food biosecurity since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746235", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746173, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17315", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many taskings for Military Aid to the Civil Authorities from his Department required the use of RAF CH-47 Chinook helicopters since 2019.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department of Health and Social Care: Military Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746172, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17314", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many taskings for Military Aid to the Civil Authorities from his Department required the use of RAF CH-47 Chinook helicopters since 2019.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs: Military Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746171, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17313", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many taskings for Military Aid to the Civil Authorities from her Department required the use of RAF CH-47 Chinook helicopters since 2019.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Military Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746288, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17312", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring manufacturers of agricultural vehicles to fit fire suppression kits.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746286, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17311", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that fire and rescue services are equipped to manage large-scale farm fires effectively.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fire and Rescue Services: Farms", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746199, "askingMemberId": 5080, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17310", "questionText": "To ask the Member for Battersea, representing the Church Commissioners, if the Church will take steps to improve the maintenance of Quarrington Hill Graveyard in County Durham.", "answeringBodyId": 9, "answeringBodyName": "Church Commissioners", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cemeteries: County Durham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746195, "askingMemberId": 5076, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17309", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make it his policy to support a female appointment as General Secretary of the United Nations.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UN Security Council: Public Appointments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746194, "askingMemberId": 5076, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17308", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will have discussions with international counterparts on the use of force against pro-democracy protesters in Georgia.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Georgia: Demonstrations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746186, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17307", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if her Department will take steps to (a) improve communication practices, (b) ensue greater sensitivity in interactions, (c) better manage families\u2019 expectations to prevent (i) delays and (ii) unnecessary distres", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coroners: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746185, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17306", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of dentists in Hazel Grove constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Hazel Grove", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746300, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17305", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that the fee paid to deliver the Special Schools Eye Care Service is not reduced so that (a) children with Special Educational Needs can receive free eye care in sch", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ophthalmic Services: Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746300", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746297, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17304", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure that touch screen card payment devices are made accessible for people with visual impairments.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746296, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to address eye care inequalities for adults with learning disabilities.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ophthalmic Services: Learning Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746275, "askingMemberId": 5064, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17302", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2024 to Question 14217 on Loans: Developing Countries, how many loan commitments have been published under the Principles for Debt Transparency since June 2023; and if she will ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Loans: Developing Countries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746262, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17301", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average salary was of each civil service grade in each Department in each year since 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746261, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17300", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions (a) Ministers, (b) special advisers, and (c) officials in (i) the Cabinet Office and (ii) 10 Downing Street have had with the Muslim Council of Britain since 5 July.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Muslim Council of Britain", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746260, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17299", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions (a) Ministers, (b) special advisers and (c) officials in her Department have had with the Muslim Council of Britain since 5 July.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Muslim Council of Britain", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746260", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746259, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17298", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions (a) Ministers, (b) special advisers, and (c) officials in her Department have had with the Muslim Council of Britain since 5 July.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Muslim Council of Britain", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746259", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746258, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Commissioner for Countering Extremism plans to review (a) teaching material for Prevent and (b) all material on gov.uk.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Commission for Countering Extremism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746258", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746257, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the location of dental surgeries in Suffolk by postcode.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Suffolk", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746257", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746256, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) dentists and (b) dental surgeries there were per capita in (a) England, (b) the East of England and (c) Suffolk in each year between 2014 and 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746256", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746255, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17294", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the location of ambulance stations by postcode (a) in West Suffolk constituency and (b) within 20 miles of that constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ambulance Services: West Suffolk", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746255", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746254, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average recorded ambulance response time was for (a) England, (b) the East of England and (c) Suffolk in each year between 2014 and 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ambulance Services: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746254", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746308, "askingMemberId": 5053, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17292", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are waiting for their asylum claims to be processed in Bolsover constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746308", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746307, "askingMemberId": 5053, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of (a) the level of transport related social exclusion and (b) cuts to community transport by Derbyshire County Council on people in Bolsover constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746307", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746303, "askingMemberId": 5053, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17290", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many care homes were referred to the Local Government and Social Care Ombudsman in (a) Bolsover constituency and (b) Derbyshire in each of the last five years; and how many w", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746303", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746285, "askingMemberId": 4942, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17284", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of allowing carers to receive covid-19 vaccinations on the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746352, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17271", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Autumn Budget 2024 on the chemicals and plastics sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Manufacturing Industries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746352", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746351, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17270", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the (a) number of factory closures and (b) levels of employment in the automotive industry.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Manufacturing Industries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746351", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746161, "askingMemberId": 4858, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17268", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department (a) made and (b) has since made an assessment of the potential impact of Autumn Budget 2024 on trends in the level of income inequality.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Income: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746160, "askingMemberId": 4858, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17267", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the terms of reference will be for her Department's review of universal credit.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit: Reviews", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746277, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17265", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what funding Thornaby on Tees will receive from the (a) Town Deal programme and (b) long-term plan for towns.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Regeneration: Thornaby", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746277", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746295, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17264", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of provision of support for children with epilepsy in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children: Epilepsy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746294, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17263", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the impact of greyhound racing on animal welfare.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Greyhound Racing: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746089, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17258", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of changes in the number of firms offering bank accounts for trusts.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746047, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17256", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether club memberships are paid for from the public purse for (a) staff, (b) contractors and (c) other employees.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Clubs: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746047", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746032, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-06T00:00:00", "uin": "17255", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases of (a) HIV and (b) AIDS have been diagnosed due to mandatory opt-out testing in hospitals.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746109, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17254", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether the British Council has to repay its pandemic loan on commercial terms.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Council: Loans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746137, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17253", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS England's commissioning guidance entitled Transcranial magnetic resonance guided focused ultrasound thalamotomy for treatment of medication-refractory essential tremor, update", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Essential Tremor: Ultrasonics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745965, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17252", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what the total amount of Government investment into type 1 diabetes disease research was in 2023-24; and which public bodies provided that investment.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diabetes: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745965", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745964, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17251", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what the total amount of Government investment into chronic kidney disease research was in 2023-24; and which public bodies provided that investment.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Kidney Diseases: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745964", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745963, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17250", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with universities on the UK\u2019s approach to research into food biosecurity since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745963", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745962, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17249", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with businesses on the UK\u2019s approach to research into food biosecurity since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745962", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745961, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17248", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with the UKRI on their approach to support research into food biosecurity since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745961", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746139, "askingMemberId": 4783, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17247", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to stop young sudden cardiac deaths; and if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) increasing the availability of ECG testing for young people", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746029, "askingMemberId": 4780, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17246", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the mean annual costs are for nurseries in England by (a) nursery class childcare settings, (b) maintained nursery schools, (c) school-based providers, (d) private group-based providers, (e) voluntary grou", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nurseries: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746029", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746118, "askingMemberId": 4777, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17245", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Pakistan government on (a) freedom of protest and (b) the (i) safety and (ii) rights of protestors.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pakistan: Politics and Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746117, "askingMemberId": 4777, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17244", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help protect British Pakistanis critical of the Pakistan government from transnational repression.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pakistan: Politics and Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746116, "askingMemberId": 4777, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17243", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential risk of transnational repression for British Pakistani critics of the Pakistan government.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pakistan: Politics and Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746099, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17242", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions her Department has had with the Department for Science, Innovation and Technology on coroners\u2019 reports of deaths associated with online suicide forums.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coroners: Suicide", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746098, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17241", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what guidance he plans to issue on whether seeking a suicide partner online is regulated under the Online Safety Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Suicide: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746097, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17240", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the number of deaths associated with pro-anorexia coaches operating online.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anorexia: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746096, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17239", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the potential (a) implications for his policies of the number of pro-anorexia coaches and (b) impact of such coaches on mental health services.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anorexia: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746095, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17238", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether his Department has set a target for reduction in the numbers of deaths by suicide associated with suicide forums following full implementation of the Online Safety Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Suicide: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746094, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17237", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of UK deaths associated with suicide forums in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Suicide: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746093, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17236", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) suicide and (b) eating disorder forums accessible to UK internet users.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Eating Disorders and Suicide: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746092, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17235", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of deaths associated with online suicide forums in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Suicide: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746037, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17234", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what his policy is on Zimbabwe's application to re-join the Commonwealth.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Zimbabwe: Commonwealth", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746037", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746036, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17233", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Commonwealth Secretariat on publication of the independent report of the Commonwealth Observer Group on Zimbabwe's elections in 202", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Zimbabwe: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746036", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746034, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17231", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has received recent representations from Hertfordshire County Council on levels of demand for in-year state school places.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Admissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746034", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745987, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17230", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of including local online news publications in the definition of local newspapers for the advertisement of planning not", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Permission: Local Press", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745987", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745975, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17229", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what plans the Government has to appoint a Special Envoy for Freedom of Religion or Belief.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Envoy on Freedom of Religion or Belief", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745975", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745980, "askingMemberId": 4676, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17226", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she plans to take to tackle disproportionate use of full strip searches during stop and searches of (a) Black, (b) Asian and (c) other ethnic minority people.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Body Searches: Ethnic Groups", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745980", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746120, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17225", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will she make an assessment of the potential merits of creating a Building Works Agency to assist with building safety remediation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buildings: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746119, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17224", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of setting building remediation targets for non-cladding building defects.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buildings: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746115, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17223", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of setting building remediation targets for (a)buildings under 11 meters and (b) non qualifying leaseholders.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buildings: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746108, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17222", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the change in the level of employer National Insurance contributions on homelessness charities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Charities: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746107, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17221", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the disparities in (a) pay and (b) prize money on the future development of (i) men\u2019s and (ii) women\u2019s football.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Football: Pay and Prize money", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746102, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17220", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of making CPR training more available to members of the public.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "CPR: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746082, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17219", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what training the NHS offers on pathological demand avoidance.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Autism: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746081, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17218", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of supporting schools to train staff to support (a) autistic students and (b) students with pathological demand avoidance.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Autism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746064, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17217", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has made representations on allegations of (a) corruption, (b) police killings, (c) disappearances, (d) torture and (e) attempts to suppress the right to protest i", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Kenya: Politics and Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746064", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746063, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17216", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to (a) help ensure and (b) verify that funding provided to governments in (i) Uganda, (ii) Kenya and (iii) other countries in sub-Saharan ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sub-Saharan Africa: Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746063", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746062, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17215", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had (a) meetings and (b) other discussions with (i) The Good Law Project and (ii) other campaigning groups on judicial independence and the rule of law in Keny", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Kenya: Judiciary", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746062", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746061, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17214", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had recent (a) meetings or (b) other discussions with human rights NGOs on reports of human rights abuses in Kenya following protests in that country.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Kenya: Human Rights", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746061", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746025, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17213", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training her Department requires call handlers to complete.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746025", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746024, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17212", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of implementing a service standard timeframe for criminal investigations by her Department into fraud.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746024", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746023, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17211", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many decision makers in her Department are working on cases of benefits fraud.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746023", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746106, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17210", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her Department's policies of the report entitled Fix the CMS: key findings from our research on child maintenance, published by Gingerbread", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Child Maintenance Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746105, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17208", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2024 to Question 14865 on British Council: Finance, what the planned expenditure of the British Council is for 2024/25.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Council: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746103, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17207", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what his Department's procedures are for informing relatives when a British national dies abroad in (a) non-suspicious and (b) suspicious circumstances.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Nationals Abroad: Death", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746050, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17206", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to improve recycling rates.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Recycling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746050", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746049, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17205", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to make recycling (a) easier and (b) cheaper for local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Recycling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746049", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746048, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17204", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to make recycling easier for residents in Slough.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Recycling: Slough", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746048", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746045, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17203", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a National Flood Resilience Centre for the purposes of (a) flood research and (b) training emergency services acro", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746044, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17202", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2024 to Question 15113 on Veterans: LGBT+ People, which recommendations have not been implemented.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: LGBT+ People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746041, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17199", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the influence of foreign funding in democratic processes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Politics and Government: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746040, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17198", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what percentage of reported incidents of shoplifting result in a (a) suspect being arrested and (b) prosecution being authorised by the CPS.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shoplifting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746039, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17197", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what percentage of reported bicycle thefts result in a (a) suspect being arrested and (b) prosecution being authorised by the CPS.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bicycles: Theft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746140, "askingMemberId": 4634, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "17196", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help (a) raise awareness of neglected tropical diseases and (b) tackle neglected tropical diseases.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746121, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17195", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions her Department has had with the Teachers Pension Scheme on delays in providing Remediable Service Statements to retired teachers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745974, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17193", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has had discussions with the Office for Budget Responsibility on the timing of the implementation of changes to the Work Capability Assessment on their projections.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Work Capability Assessment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745974", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745972, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17191", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the White Paper entitled Get Britain Working, published November 2024, whether the 384,000 additional Talking Therapies places in Priority 1 were previously (a) announced and (b) ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Mental Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745972", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746022, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17184", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where and when (a) Watchkeeper Mk 1, (b) Puma, (c) the 14 Chinook helicopters that are being retired, (d) HMS Northumberland, (e) HMS Albion, (f) HMS Bulwark, (g) RFA Wave Knight and (h) RFA Wave Ruler were last ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence Equipment: Deployment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746022", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746021, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17183", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Pumas in use in Cyprus (a) only provide a firefighting function and (b) are used for (i) search and rescue and (ii) other operational purposes.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cyprus: Puma Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746021", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746020, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17182", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the size of the (a) Regular Army, (b) RAF, (c) Royal Navy, (d) Royal Marines (e) Army Reserve, (f) RAF Reserve, (g) Royal Navy Reserve and (h) Royal Marines Reserve in 2029.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746020", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746019, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17181", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his statement of 20 November 2024 on Defence Programmes Developments, Official Report columns 287 to 289, which Army ranks will qualify for the \u00a38,000 retention payment.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Army: Incentives", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746019", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746018, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17180", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of a military solution of providing an alternative firefighting helicopter capability in Cyprus.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cyprus: Fire and Rescue Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746018", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746017, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17179", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to support armed forces personnel  who do not receive Continuity of Educational Allowance with the increase in the cost of private school fees arising from the introduction of VAT on such fees.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Private Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746017", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746016, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17178", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his statement of 20 November 2024 on Defence Programmes Developments, Official Report columns 287 to 289, if he will publish a tabulated breakdown of the forecast \u00a3500m of savings.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746016", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746015, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17177", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his statement of 20 November 2024 on Defence Programmes Developments, Official Report columns 287 to 289, what capabilities he plans to prioritise for the reinvestment of the forecast \u00a3150m of s", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746015", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746014, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17176", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of providing a (a) commercial and (b) military solution to provide an alternative firefighting helicopter capability in Cyprus.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cyprus: Fire and Rescue Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746014", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746013, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17175", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his oral statement on Defence Programmes Developments of 20 November 2024, Official Report, column 287, whether he had discussions with (a) Lord Robertson and (b) other members of the Strategic ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence Equipment: Decommissioning", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746013", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746012, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17174", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his oral statement on Defence Programmes Developments of 20 November 2024, Official Report, column 287, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of gifting the (a) 14 Chinook an", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ukraine: Military Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746012", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746011, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17173", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of retiring the Puma helicopters early on (a) Episkopi and (b) Dhekelia Garrison.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Puma Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746011", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746010, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17172", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for (a) HMS Albion, (b) HMS Bulwark, (c) RFA Wave Knight and (d) RFA Wave Ruler after they leave service.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tankers and Warships: Decommissioning", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746010", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746009, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17171", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of fixing the structural issues with HMS Northumberland.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Northumberland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746009", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746008, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17170", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the potential operational implications are of retiring the Puma helicopters early for (a) the RAF, (b) RAF Akrotiri and (c) British Forces Cyprus.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Puma Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746008", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746007, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17169", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for HMS Northumberland after she leaves service.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Northumberland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746007", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746006, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17168", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his statement of 20 November 2024 on Defence Programmes Developments, Official Report columns 287 to 289, whether he had discussions on military capability retirements with his US counterpart be", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746006", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746005, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17167", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of retiring Puma helicopters in March 2025 on capability.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Puma Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746005", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746004, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17166", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his policy that the Airbus H-145 will enter service to replace the Puma by 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Military Aircraft: Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746004", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746003, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17165", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Pumas in use in Brunei (a) only provide a support to jungle training function and (b) are used for (i) search and rescue and (ii) other operational purposes.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Puma Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746003", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746002, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17164", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the potential operational implications are of retiring Puma helicopters in March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Puma Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746002", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746001, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17163", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the potential operational implications are of providing a military solution to alternative jungle training helicopter capability in Brunei.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746001", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746000, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17162", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of a reduction in the number of Chinook helicopters on air assault operations.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinook Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746000", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745999, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17161", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of providing a (a) commercial and (b) military solution to alternative jungle training helicopter capability in Brunei.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745999", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745998, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17160", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the potential implications of retiring 14 Chinook helicopters early are on the ability of (a) Joint Helicopter Command, (b) the Chief of Joint Operations, (c) 16 Air Assault Brigade Combat Team, (d) 16 Air M", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinook Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745998", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745997, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17159", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the potential operational implications are of retiring 14 Chinook helicopters early for (a) 16 Air Assault Brigade Combat Team, (b) the Air Manoeuvre Task Force, (c) Joint Helicopter Command, (d) the Global ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinook Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745997", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745996, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17158", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the retirement of 14 Chinook helicopters on the capability of the armed forces.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinook Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745996", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745995, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17157", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the potential operational implications are of retiring 14 Chinook helicopters early.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinook Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745995", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745994, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17156", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to gift (a) cannibalised parts of and (b) complete Watchkeeper Mk 1 platforms to allies.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Watchkeeper WK450", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745994", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745993, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17155", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of retiring Watchkeeper Mk 1 on the personnel of 47th Regiment Royal Artillery.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Watchkeeper WK450", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745993", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745992, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17154", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the retirement of Watchkeeper Mk 1 on the capability of the armed forces.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Watchkeeper WK450", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745992", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745991, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17153", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the removal of Watchkeeper Mk 1 on the 47th Regiment Royal Artillery.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Watchkeeper WK450", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745991", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745990, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17152", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the potential operational implications are of retiring Watchkeeper Mk 1 in March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Watchkeeper WK450", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745990", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745989, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17151", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the potential operational implications are of retiring RFA (a) Wave Knight and (b) Wave Ruler in March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "RFA Wave Knight and RFA Wave Ruler", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745989", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745988, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17150", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the status is of the planned multi-role support ships.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Multi-role Ocean Surveillance Ships", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745988", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745984, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17147", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the retirement of HMS Northumberland on the capability of the armed forces prior to delivery of the first Type 26.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Northumberland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745984", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745983, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17146", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the potential operational implications are of retiring HMS Northumberland in March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Northumberland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745983", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745982, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17145", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to announce financial details of the increase to Continuity of Educational Allowance.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Private Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745982", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746125, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17142", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total cost to the public purse was of out of court settlements for employment tribunal cases across Government in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Employment Tribunals Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746079, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17140", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the material considerations were that satisfied the call-in criteria for the proposed Chinese Embassy near the Tower of London.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746078, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17139", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the additional revenue to be raised from properties with rateable value of \u00a3500,000 or above in order to be able to set lower multipliers for retail, hospitality and leisure properties ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746077, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17138", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the decision to apply a higher multiplier to all properties with a rateable value of \u00a3500,000 or above on (a) large supermarkets and (b) department stores.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Retail Trade: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746077", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746076, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17137", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the number of properties that the proposed new multiplier above \u00a3500,000 Rateable Value will apply to by (a) special categories and (b) sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746076", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746075, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17136", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish an impact assessment for the proposed application of a higher multiplier to properties with a rateable value of \u00a3500,000 or above.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746075", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746074, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17135", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish an impact assessment for the proposed reduction in business rate relief for retail, hospitality and leisure businesses in England.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746074", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746073, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17134", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what is the (a) mean and (b) median Rateable Value of hereditaments over \u00a3500,000.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746073", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746072, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17133", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the level of the (a) lower multiplier for retail, hospitality and leisure hereditaments from April 2026 and (b) higher multiplier for hereditaments above \u00a3500,000 Rateable Value; and wh", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746072", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746071, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17132", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish a list of the Rateable Value of each pub in England by (a) address, (b) local authority and (c) Rateable Value.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Houses: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746071", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746070, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17131", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance she has issued on whether (a) supermarkets, (b) hotels and (c) department stores with a rateable value over \u00a3500,000 will be liable to pay the new business rates rateable value multiplier surcharge fro", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746070", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746069, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17130", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the debate on the Non-Domestic Rating (Multipliers and Private Schools) Bill of 25 November 2024, Official Report, column 594, whether the Retail, Hospitality a", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746069", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746068, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17129", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance her Department issues on whether a planning application previously been rejected by a planning authority can be resubmitted without substantive changes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746068", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746067, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17128", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 58 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of local government restructuring on social care (a) delivery an", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746067", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746066, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17127", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans not to commence provisions of the Levelling Up and Regeneration Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Levelling-up and Regeneration Act 2023", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746066", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745970, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17126", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.80 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October, what proportion of the \u00a3120\u00a0million is new funding.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745970", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745968, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17124", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which provisions of the Levelling Up and Regeneration Act 2024 have (a) been and (b) are due to be commenced.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Levelling-up and Regeneration Act 2023", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745968", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745966, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17123", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment has the Valuation Office Agency made of the potential impact of the 2026 business rates revaluation on businesses, broken down by (a) special category code and (b) each English region.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745966", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745959, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17122", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government records the details of meetings Ministers have at party conferences.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Conferences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745959", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745971, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17121", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the (a) expulsion of a UK diplomat by Russia and (b) travel bans issued by Russia on UK officials and Mi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Diplomatic Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745971", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745967, "askingMemberId": 4277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17120", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2024 to Question 12460 on AUKUS, whether he has received Sir Stephen Lovegrove\u2019s report on AUKUS; and when he plans to publish that report.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "AUKUS", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745967", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746135, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17119", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data his Department collects on the safety outcomes of people in prison who are screened as having a previously acquired brain injury.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brain: Injuries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746134, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17118", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data his Department collects on the health outcomes of people in prison who are screened as having a previously acquired brain injury.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brain: Injuries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746133, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17117", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance is available for prison officers for dealing with people entering custody found to have a previously acquired brain injury.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Injuries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746132, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17116", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance is available for healthcare professionals in prisons for dealing with people entering custody found to have a previously acquired brain injury.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brain: Injuries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746131, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17115", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people aged (a) 14-17, (b) 18-25 and (c) 26 and over who enter prison custody and are assessed for brain injury within seven days are found to have an acquired brain", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brain: Injuries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746130, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17114", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people aged (a) 14-17, (b) 18-25 and (c) 26 and over who enter prison custody and are screened for brain injury within 24 hours are found to have an acquired brain i", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brain: Injuries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746129, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17113", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people aged (a) 14-17, (b) 18-25 and (c) 26 and over who enter prison custody receive an assessment for previously acquired brain injury within seven days.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brain: Injuries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746128, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17112", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people aged (a) 14-17, (b) 18-25 and (c) 26 and over who enter prison custody receive a screening for previously acquired brain injury within 24 hours.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brain: Injuries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746114, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17111", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he plans to take steps with his international counterparts to review Israel's access to the F-35 Global Supply Chain pool.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Israel: F-35 Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746113, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17110", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to help ensure the necessary conditions for (a) safe and (b) effective humanitarian operations by UNRWA in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746112, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17109", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for the UK government\u2019s support for the UN\u2019s UNRWA mission in Gaza, of the approval by the Israeli Knesset of legi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: UNRWA", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746111, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17108", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the capability of the UN World Food Programme to deliver food aid to Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Food Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746110, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17107", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies on the supply of aid to Gaza of the decision by the United Nations Relief and Works Agency to pause", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746087, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17106", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to require combined mayoral authorities to publish evaluation reports on individual funding programmes in a standardised format.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Combined Authorities: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746087", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746086, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17105", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress her Department has made on developing accountability processes for institutions that secure single funding settlements at the Spending Review.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746086", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746085, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17104", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to publish outcomes of annual discussions with combined mayoral authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Combined Authorities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746085", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746084, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17103", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to publish (a) metrics and (b) outcomes for the spending performance of combined mayoral authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Combined Authorities: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746083, "askingMemberId": 4269, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17102", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what data her Department holds on the outcomes of funding provided to combined mayoral authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Combined Authorities: Local Government Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746055, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17101", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of changes in the level of anti-Christian (a) discrimination and (b) hate crimes in Europe.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Europe: Religious Freedom", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746055", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746054, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17100", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have had meetings with Ahmadiyya Muslim representatives in London in the last six months.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign and Commonwealth Office: Ahmadiyya", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746054", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745979, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17099", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many women from the three lowest multiple deprivation deciles donated eggs between 2011 and 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "IVF: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745979", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745978, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17098", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what impact assessment his Department made of the increase in the amount paid to egg donors on 1 October 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "IVF: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745978", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745977, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17097", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of a minimum age of 25 for egg donation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "IVF: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745977", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745976, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17096", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of a ban on advertisements for egg donors.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "IVF: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745976", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745958, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17095", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of flexible working patterns offered to enable parents to (a) work and (b) afford the costs of childcare.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childcare: Flexible Working", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745958", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746144, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17094", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Autumn Budget 2024 on the aerospace sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aerospace Industry", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746143, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17093", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Autumn Budget 2024 on the automotive sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Manufacturing Industries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746142, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-05T00:00:00", "uin": "17092", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Autumn Budget 2024 on the advanced manufacturing sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Manufacturing Industries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746027, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17090", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with representatives of health charities since the Autumn Budget 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health: Charities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746027", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746080, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17088", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial support she plans to provide to the Early Years sector to help manage the impact of proposed changes to employer National Insurance contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pre-school Education: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746053, "askingMemberId": 3997, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17086", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if his Department will take steps to accelerate the (a) clearance and (b) restoration of legacy nuclear sites.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Radioactive Waste", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746053", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746052, "askingMemberId": 3997, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17085", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to help tackle (a) illegal landfill sites and (b) waste crime.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Waste: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746052", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746028, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17084", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the increase in school funding in the 2025-26 academic year (a) per pupil, (b) in real terms per pupil based on the GDP deflator and (c) in real terms per pupil based on Retail Pri", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Per Capita Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746028", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1745981, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17083", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 Nov 2024 to Question 15640 on Mental Health Services: Schools, whether the plan to introduce access to a specialist mental health professional in every school differs f", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Schools", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1745981", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746033, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17082", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to update the Civil Contingencies Act 2004 in the light of the threat from Russia.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Contingencies Act 2004", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746033", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746136, "askingMemberId": 1466, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17081", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2024 to Question 14931 on War Widows Pension Scheme, how many (a) spouses and (b) civil partners have claimed compensation via the War Widows Pension Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "War Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746123, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17076", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to spend the \u00a3300 million allocated to her Department for further education in the Autumn Budget 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Further Education: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746122, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to help ensure that district councils receive business rates from (a) all energy infrastructure and (b) sub stations located within their boundaries.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "District Councils: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746065, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential impact of the Terminally Ill Adults (End of Life) Bill on the NHS budget.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Terminally Ill Adults (End of Life) Bill ", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746065", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746060, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many age assessments of people arriving on small boats and seeking asylum have taken place in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Age", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746060", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746059, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17072", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Border Security Command is taking to assess the age of asylum seekers arriving on small boats.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Age", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746059", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746058, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many justices of the peace served at Boston Magistrates court in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Magistrates: Boston", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746058", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746057, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17070", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to reduce the (a) risk of and (b) impact from fires in agricultural vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746057", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746056, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to support veterans in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire with (i) housing and (ii) education and skills training.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746056", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746051, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils in primary schools in England were suspended in each of the last three academic years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupil Exclusions: Primary Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746051", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746031, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17067", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many fixed penalty notices have been handed out for spitting in (a) Lincolnshire and (b) England in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Spitting: Fines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746031", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746030, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many fixed penalty notices have been handed out for littering in (a) Lincolnshire and (a) England in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Litter: Fines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1746091, "askingMemberId": 39, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "17063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding her Department plans to provide for the Listed Places of Worship Grant scheme in the 2025-26 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1746091", "method": "GET"}]}]